Where the fake get loud when the views dry up
Gotta hate the one crooked, gotta sermon half-baked
Say I'm praying for you while these screenshots get saved
Fake are concerned and their boys poison in the cup
Say I hate drama while they wind it up
Got pearls in a death grip
Clutch, clutch, talk real big
Why don't you take some of the clap money,
get YouTube premium light?
I think it's like $7.50 and you don't get commercials
and stuff, but then, you know, little Miss B
that chimes in.
Well, then you take money for clapping,
you take money for clapping.
And then like this Down syndrome,
not no financial name with Down syndrome,
but like, I don't know that guy that,
oh, he takes money but he doesn't make it.
Well, how can I take what I don't make?
I checked I didn't make seventy five dollars in a day recently clapping three people
I don't know but oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Oh, come on, take the panel, you coward!
Um, well, invest me that if you want me to take the panel,
or else I don't want to make you another,
you know, a pair of Nikes, you know?
Oh!
Mm.
It's just like so, like,
and then it's like, always, I mean, I'm sorry, like, you know.
What is it like? I'm looking at a book. I'm looking at a black and I know I've had like, you know
Icon up or something, but I'm looking absolutely back black screen
I think like playing like pebs his voice and stuff like and they're talking about
me all the time and in the
Bring up all this. I don't know. It's like I
Can't take that show. I mean, it's like
The only good content on it is mine basically
I mean, it's like, no, there's other people of good content and stuff, but it's like,
I'm talking about him, like, oh, like, I play like a five minute song that I made, you know,
everyone's running out, literally, there's like 100 people in there listening to like
mumble rap that sounds like it was like, and that which I'm pretty sure was 99% sure was
Anyway, anyway, any hero, anyhow, I'm the fucking bad guy.
I'm the bad guy.
Seems like a little bit, like, I don't know.
I have zero people in the chat and it's like that's the intelligence level of like
I'd rather not even like be pan I don't know but I'm not going on the panel again unless I have
a free vest and so that's it so you got me off the show I can't be on the show anyway for two
seconds so what a lot but it's a difference just stupid
Beta, have you ever heard of a mirror?
Because you look in it and you'll see maybe this.
Maybe when you look in the mirror, you'll see this beta.
And this is not doxing, by the way.
This was a picture of you on cam, on stream, okay?
Maybe look in a mirror beta, here's what you might see.
Look in the mirror, Sam-Man.
And we're gonna see if you look in the mirror, Sam-Man.
Here's what you're gonna see, Sam-Man.
Wanna see what you're gonna look like in the mirror?
Maybe like this.
Maybe.
Good, God Almighty.
You can't even afford McDonald's. I'm getting McDonald's all week.
Shout out to Mr. McQueen, my buddy.
I'm getting McDonald's all week.
What?
I mean, it's so dumb.
Anyone just got this copy cost?
Free
Let's go and they refill it for free. I paid 99 cents this morning to get a coffee
And I'm gonna go back like five times and get a free refill on it
W
What I can't help I'm smart
So no one's gonna say hi or anything it's hate watchers I know
It's like no one understands, it's like they don't understand, like, things can be taken
out of context, you know?
I can be like reacting and turning back to like some shit and so maybe that's why I said
some of the things I said, maybe like, you know, death is a metaphor for like, you know,
death of like the channel or something like that because I'm constantly under attack.
I'm talking about like the people that are flagging and stuff like that. I'm not talking about
but um hey what's up fleet bag good to see you all right they're just like so silly
great divide is upon a sloppy joe a great divide is happening
but guys it's really cool um I do want to thank um
someone in someone in my heart but um
not to be mushy or whatever, but I want to thank
Alexandra Mayer's of IRL News Time,
IP2wiki.info, Alexandra Mayer's,
those are her channels that I have off my top of my head.
She reviewed my codecs today,
and I really appreciate that.
And she, I respect her opinion a lot
because she didn't have a wiki up before the IP2 wiki, I guess.
And...
Uh, hey ladies purse. Hey sloppy Joe. Hey Felipe. She had the and uh, and she and she went through
She did a she a really nice review and I just want to thank her for having a have a look at it and sharing and stuff and you know
She gave really good advice. You know, it's not done. You know, it's in the process
There's like it's not you know, it is a little bit
I'm of uh
You know
What's up white Snoop Dogg? Hey yo
Snoop Dogg in jail.
Did Snoop Dogg get arrested or is that a dream or something like that?
Did I see Snoop Dogg get arrested for the murder of Tupac or something?
Is that true?
That's the last I saw of Tupac, I think, unless I was dreaming.
Sometimes I get things mixed up because I have a very active dream life.
Hello, hello, hello, hello there.
She should have gone that way.
If they would have gone that way, they would have gone straight to the castle.
Do you think of Snoop Dogg arrests for AI?
Maybe.
Oh, and then he's like, there's a picture of Samman and Bita.
And it's like, you know, I think he was pretty much AI.
It's like they're like a Disneyland or something.
And Samman is like looking like clear skin.
Like, you know, just good looking.
He's going frowning and then Bita's on his back.
And he's probably frowning because, you know,
he's a little bit heavy these days.
It was AI, but she still didn't look. Oh my gosh
You know what you should look at like a trip trip kicks
AI's would be that those
Those make her look pretty those are flattering, but um, I don't know who made that Disney Disney one
I don't think they use they definitely I think Sam I must have made it because he looked okay, but
Be the looks just awful. It's just awful
mean spruce it up a little lady I mean come on that's why he's frowning he has
this like ogre on his back I'm sorry but I don't want to be cruel but ay-ay-ay-ay-ay
good god almighty oh good god I miss my
Times it went oh it's 12 14. Oh good Lord. I mean it's like maybe maybe I'll have an early day
I did buy a couple drinks. I'm kind of feeling like drinking them now
You may have an early early night
Five in the afternoon
I got I got I got I got some good shit. This is a nice smash peach and mango and a pineapple and strawberry
I'm gonna drink them while they're cold
But I got a coffee left and stuff.
Yeah, OK, I promised today, and oh, and they're like, oh,
they're like, oh, is transcripts out?
Like, it's like, I'm doing, first of all, most of the transcripts
aren't really AI transcripts, and most of them
are just taken right up on YouTube.
Right, you got a couple cans of content here.
Ayo, Ayo, if you want to help me get a couple more cans,
you know, I'm doing another sale today on Clap Tokens.
It'll be a limited time sale.
Until I sell, I guess I'm gonna sell five
of the discounted Clap Tokens, $10 each.
You get 24 hour bans of the panel and stuff.
Pre-roll joints, you got a couple from the local use store.
That's awesome, you know.
I would like it to smoke a joint today,
that I would really sleep.
If I smoked a joint today,
since I haven't smoked joints or weed in a couple weeks,
I would sleep like a baby, you know?
Yeah, I mean it's like and I don't want to strike channels
But he's just so rude about like, you know playing my content
Then I can't like respond really on panel because it's like I get clapped and then it's like and then he's like so
bloating about it and then it's like and then they like
You know, I wasn't even complaining about his clap system at all. I have a clap system, right?
But and you know if he wants to play my content and stuff, you know, I'm really like kind of against
striking anything just on principle because I don't like it done to me and
stuff but I mean he doesn't use attribution he doesn't like even like
he never says oh there's cults of psyche or anything like that or oh shit
doesn't say anything I mean he like he like edit off my logo and stuff if I
have a logo up on it and it's like and then he'll sit there in the list make fun
of me and stuff and
And then the chat all gangs up on me and except for like a few people like I like I saw some people were like in there
Being cool, you know, like my friend my friend. I mean, I've seen some friends in there
I think they're trying to light up a intense right now
But yeah, they go there mean and it's like and then they're saying oh they're gonna just like my chance up and so that's why it's kind of like
can't even like fucking feel comfortable putting up my own stuff because it's like then they've given me
and so it's like they've given me permission and stuff but
i don't know i just like i just like you know
trying to be okay you know the coke ready now i'm gonna i'm trying to light my instance i don't
have cocaine i can't really afford cooking it's a little bit expensive
I can't even afford weed.
I could afford two cigars today
and a couple beers and a McDonald's fries
and other drinks, not beers.
A couple of fries.
I got a free sausage biscuit sandwich this morning I ate.
Yeah.
I mean, if I was with Alexander McQueen,
I'm sure you'd have an eight ball.
I wouldn't, I'd talk in.
party with McQueen and stuff for sure, but California it's like a little bit too expensive.
And also like Coke doesn't really do anything for me like it it's basically like I get the same
feeling basically from going to the dentist's office. My mouth gets numb a little bit. I get a
Nice feeling in my brain for like 10 minutes and that's it. It's done
And then I end up like having to snort off of things on a toilet seat
Or so it's just a pack of a toilet after go every 10 minutes that the bathroom and stuff that it's just like you dangerous now
Yeah, well, I don't have I don't I don't have anything. I don't have anything
I have incense and resin and a book and tobacco. I scrape off my table and shit
But you know what?
That's okay. It's not it's not like, you know, drugs are bad. Okay
Don't do drugs. Okay
For some premium frankincense
Put some of this on
Okay, oh
There we go. I got a little bit of them for the rest of this copal or copal armor.
Yeah, he's like the leader of like the wine mommy army, you know.
Hey Sam! That's my Christine Boyce. Hey Sam!
Some people think he's cool and funny.
Yeah, I mean, it's like I have a cat. I have a nice mattress. I like a lot of mattress
I was pretty well on Etsy selling readings a few years ago. It's like now. It's like hard to
Really hard to sell them on Etsy because it's like there's so many free readings on on YouTube that people do and there's also like, you know
Like a lot of it's like people on there. I love just having having like a little
Trouble recently, but I was doing really well at one point and I would
about about a whole mattress and I
And I hardly have ever slept on it, you know cats sleep on them more than I do and
You know he wants to watch clips of angry women and make commentary like he's the moral leader
I know isn't it weird?
Like isn't this person in Rikers Island prison and stuff like
Like I've been to jail, like I've said, I took a shower in jail with much Mexicans and like hung out with peckerwoods and you know
For like a few days for a weekend
You know
It wasn't nothing
You can look up my criminal record if you want. I don't care because it's not really nothing there
It's just it's just basically not basically it is just misdemeanors and shit. It wasn't even close to anything
You know, it's like the same as like
basically like
traffic tickets and shit
And it's not black either and no one has a problem with him saying n-word and everything but it's like if I say it
It's it's racist, right because white people aren't allowed to say anything
And I know I'm not if I use it. It was not in a racial way
It was like in a in a way like, you know, there's there's different looks on the word and stuff
I'm not getting into semantics with these people
Yeah, the moral ganks to nuka nuka. I'll say nuka nuka
knucklehead
My knuckles have more brain cells in him than his brain
So I must feel sorry. Hey, I want to go to NYC Alex McQueen. You want to hang out with me?
I'm gonna come when it snort a bunch of cocaine and like hang out in New York. I'm down
We can go to McDonald's we can like you know
Yeah, you can do IRL if you want and I don't you know he's brown at least. Oh
Does that make a difference? Oh, so I'm like what is so I need to be like a little bit
I need to get a more of a tan or something
monster
really
He's more black does that make him more black than me I
Do have like point zero one percent subs to here in Africa in my DNA so probably more
Then I'm here. Oh, oh
Rudy really getting old little man. Oh
Rudy
There's a little cough baby. Oh
Baby, I don't have enough melanin. Well, yeah, if I get a spray tan
You know, like tan mom, I think, is like, you know, can say it.
No one ever gave her a problem either, and she's just tan.
I don't have enough melanin.
Well, I don't know about that.
Like, I'm a little bit like, I got a little bit of color in my skin.
You can see, but you see my blue, my blue veins.
They got blue blood royalty.
But, um, see that, see the blue veins?
You kind of see him. I'm so white I'm blue. I'm red-white and blue like the American flag, basically.
Babe, are you okay?
Now, I'm getting a little concerned because I haven't seen Trixie today.
And so, let's say a prayer for Mr. Trix.
He always, sometimes it does leave for a little while and stuff.
He's been kind of going out more recently. It's okay, are you okay babe?
Babe give me a little cough
I've been with a I've had a black guy inside of me, right? So I've had black inside exactly exactly
But so is Sandman to be fair
Right
I'm sure he took some up the butt and he was in Rikers
Pretty 90 more than 99% sure. Yeah, so
Does that man's head, you know, he so maybe he can use the word okay, cuz he said so he said some black ticks inside of him
Probably more than me too. So maybe he does have more of a right
Okay, okay
I'm not saying I'm gay and it's like I'll say that to you it's like and then I'm not putting like one time I got like
a show taken down for like oh you know you said some like something terrible or
something and or someone did right and I went and looked it was me talking about
gay people I'm like you have a pink hook I know you know what the interesting
though is like some Latinos
They have like black dicks. Have you ever seen that? I don't know if you and I like I've seen that like in person
I'll put this in personal my mouth, but no, but I've seen it in the jail, too
And like some of them have black dicks
They're like they're like black from the waist down or something. I don't know
They also have that anteater thing. The voice by the way is I did too much Christine imitations
And so and also yelling at like screaming and stuff and so it does take a little toll on the old vocal cords
But you know, I can still like speak my I can do low, but I can't go high I go high it starts
He's he the type to watch WWE while eating a hot dog without a bun. Well, I
Don't like WWE but I do like
some of the
amateur kind of
Like wrestling there's one thing called viva la what's it called?
It's like some Mexican, there's a Mexican one, but it's really, I forgot what it's called and stuff, but
It's like a really good
It's really funny and stuff and they, it's like a circus kind of thing and they have drag queens and they, it's like they have, it's a Mexicans drag, it's like a big, it's like my fantasy, basically.
Luchador, it's Luchador kind of but it's like it's like uh it's called like lucha something
It's like and it's in Los Angeles or like and like they have like certain shows
Even a lot of lucha. I forgot what it's called, but it's like I haven't watched it in quite a while, but
What about sumo?
I'm not into like really obese japanese men
but
I do like seeing their, they have nice butts sometimes.
Sometimes they're pretty athletic and they look okay.
Hey, just, hey, kids go.
Hey, I'm Alkster.
These perks won't be saved.
Maya, you got some great people in here.
Yeah, I saw Felipe, I see Damien.
Yeah, he has a pink hook.
I see Nick Johnson.
I see by Mr. Names are I see devil eyes. Thanks for coming to the premiere earlier of the new Psyche haters club 2.0 video
I see all day every day. I see I can't say KN EEG are are are and I'm not gonna say that name, but
I see chibi chibi I see sloppy Joe
They a lot of friends in here
Okay
You're like when I say your full name, but then I get in trouble. Okay. You're lucky. I let you in the chat. Oh my gosh
Oh, he's getting so old
baby
Getting a little old
There you go a little little booger in here. That's not Lola brought in a mouse and
It was kind of like
Eek a mouse. Hey Sadie star. So you good to see ya
You're I know I bet you're a nice guy. I think you are a nice guy. Do you know you never said anything wrong in my chat or anything?
The people a lucha, right? It's called the it's like a it's in it's like a I think it's called Viva la lucha or something like that and
I
Have a Mexican wrestler mask. I don't know where I put it. It's a good round. I was looking for last night and stuff
I want to get my speedo soon when I wash. I mean I have to wash the speedo because I work for like two days in a row
but I when I am it's in the washing machine, but um
Yeah, um
And I want to put on and I have a Mexican wrestler clown. I think I might be in this place in my closet
some of our, I think it's buried under some of my laundry, so I'll find that later. But
I look kind of cute in it. I don't have a bad body. Like I don't, I'm not like, I mean,
I do have a kind of a bad body. I'm like way too skinny, but you know, I have like my cool tattoo.
You know, I'm a little bony up there, but I do have like, you know, these great abs.
Pretty like perfect, right? Sorry.
Not I have kind of a flat butt and stuff like thing that is but you know if I
the right angle
Yeah, I saw the new cat pretty cool. I
Got it. Thank you just spunky for sponsoring this tap. I
Love it. I love it. It's perfect
There you go looking good
So, let me, hold on, let me put out my link.
Let me see.
Copy.
Thank you, Modo guys.
There you go, I'm gonna pin the link
and I'm gonna try to pin it back on.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah.
I think he was spunky for sponsoring like the Ubers and the tattoo and you know everything oh
My gosh, so bronze chicken was like saying oh this this guy
He calls the tattoo parlor and he says I'm gonna be streaming
Can I and he said I asked for a free tattoo?
No, I said, do you think I could get a little discount? They gave me like 125. I am banned everybody
Nick does have good ideas.
Bringing people off the street for content into my house.
Do you know that some of the weird people walking around here?
Yeah, rooms here, no one's banned.
I mean, I'm trying to do like unbanned
unless you're like doxing or something like that
in your name, I'm not gonna care, you know.
I'm trying to like let people just say what they want to say in the chat off the panel. I'll be like
You know in charge. I'm basically I have a I just have a couple a couple mods and
You know you come in peace, okay, thank you. Is your brother know you're here
You promise? Okay. Okay. I mean, I don't have a problem with you. I just like, you know
And I know you're like, you know, but your brother knows you here. Oh, there's my call. Hi
What lie?
I see you
Does everyone see my call or am I lying? Am I a liar guys?
I'm lying
What's the lie tell me the lie again, Mike
I see you, I'm lying.
I ban all minorities.
Well, do you know that Broom Gang is Puerto Rican?
Do you know that?
See, he had to change that.
Who are the mods?
Well, McQueen's one of them, the others are secrets.
Yeah, there's are some secrets I also have a robot mod
That's for me to know and you guys to find out but all the same McQueen's a mod. Yeah
Alex is a
And Alan's doesn't hide anybody like everyone was saying, oh, he's hiding everybody he timed out some people for 10 seconds
Just being an asshole because he wants to have fun and stuff and then some people that were threatening our lives and stuff and
The robot. Yeah, I have a robot mod
The robot
Unfortunately, I'm out of I'm out of credits for the program I use for it
Like I have to like refill credit sometimes because it goes by this API and stuff
Um, yeah, he, I mean, hey, we all go a little crazy sometimes.
Don't you know, Alex did hide you from being nice to the one lady who was in the panel.
Well, I, I, I, I had hide everybody.
Like there's nobody hidden right now.
Well, I pay even better attention now.
The thing is I'm paying attention, but on the stream yard, you don't see the mod activity.
And so I'd have to go to like my phone and go through and look at it.
But you know hey, thank you for the love and the hearts. I see the hearts and I see big people with big eyes and all that kind of stuff
That's cool. Thank you
McDonald's
well, also
extreme loyalty and
Going into lion's den to defend me and stuff like that like basically
And maybe some maybe McDonald's all week
Maybe
Your channel's blocked in Sam Ants chat. Are you is that because
Are you doxing somebody if something I really guys you have to kind of kind of point out to me if someone's doxing?
Or if there's some kind of like something we're going on like is I don't always know everybody's like I don't know
Everyone thinks I'm this like master doxer or whatever. I don't like doxing
I don't think what I've done is doxing like people have said is doxing. I everything I've done is like
been pretty much stuff that's that been out in public and stuff and
Not someone any of us know okay, but is it you and
Yeah, if guys if you want to get cat food if you just don't want to support the channel
I'll also give you if you buy me cat food. I'll give you a couple of clap tokens. It's on my with Amazon wishlist
There's just a big box of first skis of wet food on there right now
You archive. Okay?
Okay
You archive one well
Don't know why you're blocked. I don't know you get to ask him that
So shout out for skis
Top of the morning. Yeah, I've had a couple copies. This is my second coffee. I also have a couple drinks
Hey, let's welcome our first guest all the way from heaven
You know, some people may may call him a little evil, but you know what? He's my friend
He might be a whole year than now, but he's my kind of holy and
Emphasis I'm just gonna get too far
Yo, hey, what's oh fuck hold on? Oh
Hello, I cammed up. I actually look it on Chico. How you doing? I am fabulous. How are you today gaudy?
That's too bad, bro. Just check it in on you seeing what's good Santa Claus, right?
It just looks like Santa Claus to me. Yeah, that wasn't me don't fucking for yourselves
That was oh my god, you know, that's what you look like
Yeah, yeah, that's exactly what I look like. Yeah, let me show you again. Hold on. Hold on. Let me show you again. Oh
My god
Yeah, yeah, that's me
White man like Confucius
That's my screw face. Oh
That's what you me looks like
Also
No, she's dog, right? Oh, I don't yeah, she's dog. She does. I know you're listening bitch
What's going on man, you're feeling good
You felt like shit the last three days. I know but my throat is because of this Christine imitation and then it's like
You know, my throat has gotten terrible
Yeah, you know, I'm afraid I don't you know only saying this because I'm a friend of yours, but I'm afraid you're getting obsessed with Christine
I'm a son of Chris
Do you know she had like like literally like a four-hour live with like several people on the panel just
Dedicated talking about me mentioning my family mentioning my you know why right? You know watch if he loves you she loves you dude
Yeah, she fucking loves you who does who would devote a four-hour stream to somebody?
Talking about them for four fucking hours
Bronzeberg did a nine-hour stream about me and be there you go
I mean, it's like there's stuff. I'm like fucking there's more streams about me than anybody else. I've ever seen my life
I'm like, you're getting up there with Manson levels
Everything's all about me. Yeah. Well, so you should be happy man
No, no, no, no, no, no see don't go fucking crazy now
So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I saw that that was good. Okay. That was nice to spunky, huh? She fucking paid for that
That's fucking nice, that's good people man right there. I give a shit, but you know, I know she's good
I love her. I love her
She might Christine might have a crush on me. She's a married woman. Okay, and it's okay, dude
You're gonna let these women fantasize sometimes. They like to just you know, think about things. Let them think about it
Yeah, they always fantasize about things. They can't have let let her have this
Christine's good people listen. Don't get me wrong. I love Christine. I don't think that about her too
And I was like to be honest. It's kind of like I just kind of had a giggle at this
That's why I played the shows like I don't play the shows I just played the transcripts
I have a giggle about it, but she does get a little bit personal when she's like
Well, you know what his mom probably doesn't have anything to do with him
He's just a black sheep and his family hates them and he gets paid every Friday and he's I mean
It's like he's just been making pulling shit out of their heard their ass about me that is really none of their business
It is like I ever bring up anything besides saying
You know, Christine said to her son to jump off a bridge, but then she's like, well,
that's talking about the competitive sport of bridge jumping.
When I first came here, Christine was part of the show.
And I remember she was very supportive.
She was trying to like assist you in running the show.
I remember that.
It was a little, it was a little mothering though.
It was a very mothering.
I mean, I appreciate, I respect, listen, I respect grandmothers.
But the thing is, she said she had her, her, her vagina lips were bigger than six cock.
Like that's an appropriate thing for a grandchild.
Did she say that?
Did she really say that?
It is so.
She said that, I swear to God.
She said, I don't know what to think.
I don't know what to fucking think.
I don't know either.
It's like, what if you're not,
but she had nine grandchildren.
I don't mean to like say that,
but she says this all the time.
What are these nine grandchildren ever?
Someone, some jerk.
I don't know.
It's just like,
It would be traumatizing Christine Christine. I know you're listening get up here and fucking refute this son of a bitch
Please because he has no fucking right talking about your fucking vagina lips
Right talking about that one
Dick well obviously that means it's fucking tiny right that means she's a fucking tiny
That's what she's saying. Think of think about it
I don't want to think about, I don't, I don't want to f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f**k it, f
That's the trip. Holy shit. Wow. I didn't expect this last person ever. What's up, kid?
You've gone great. He's great. He's here to expose me.
I only have to say hello for 10 seconds and I'm going because of my microphone.
Are you going to expose me? Expose me.
Have a nice day, man. Nice one, Psyche.
That's it. Good to see you, man. Good to see you, man. Have a good one.
Oh, Jesus man. I dodged the bull. He I thought he's gonna come up here and expose me. He was gonna expose the shit out of me this guy
Holy fuck. Oh, well, thankfully you didn't do that. Oh fuck
That was a nice cameo. Well, it's you know, it's good to have cameos like that 10-second cameo
Yeah, yeah, he's from that island over there like the loveboat remember the loveboat they come on the show what we got I smash
You're not fuck you're gonna get drunk early tonight, huh? It's not nearly
1242 you know, it's like, you know, three o'clock in the afternoon somewhere a
Little afternoon. Yeah, nothing wrong with that
No, they call they call it happy hour happy hour between 12 and 6 right? Yeah
This is that's when the best deals are I love happy hour by the way
And you also love people talking about you
I guess I reconciled with in a certain way say it
Made peace, guess.
I think I know.
It starts with an A, ends with an A.
You're correct.
You got a beautiful woman that loves you.
She said it.
Oh, I don't know if you saw the Dear John video.
I just watched it actually.
I just watched it a little while ago.
Very touching.
It was touching, it was, it was.
That's somebody who cares about you right there.
It was like, because you know what?
Cause I was like, sometimes I think of myself.
People say get a job. It's like they're like, okay, we're McDonald's even I was like, that's what I can do
I work McDonald's um, you know, you know Alexander says
How about you be a screenwriter or director? She's you know, it's like she has like a she thinks
Highly of me. Okay, and I saw she sees in you. She sees in you what I see in her so much potential
So much greatness that you know, it's way beyond this bullshit that you guys do on here
He does whatever she does for her reasons. You do whatever you do for your reasons, but you guys
See the reconciliation or not reconcile it was kind of like the the truce I would say it was like more of a truce
It was more of a
She let me talk. She like she talked bad. She like, you know, we had a conversation. I apologize
I said she doesn't owe me an apology because I said I said terrible things like and me and she was more
Kind of joking and trolling with me and I kind of like feel like I went too far with some of the things I said
I feel bad, but um, you know, and then today I see she's like reviewing the cult codex in like a very
barren balanced way and it's like
Wow, it's like, you know, I just appreciate it. I just appreciate it
And well, she's right about the the group think once you get involved with the group think and you get all fucked up with that group
Yeah, she said she said you know one thing she said was like, you know some people that should have had my back and should have been my friends
Have been pretty cruel to me and I think she's she saw that finally like you know
She was alluding to somebody who was that?
You know who I didn't get it right away. I kind of think I know but I'm not sure who was
Was it a B, I don't think it was a B more like a P P, okay
She didn't say the name she said you know who I'm talking about
Definitely not it wasn't the B
Okay, is it what's the people who starts with the PM? I can't even I never mind never mind never mind
I don't want to say it in the in somebody say in the chat
I don't I don't want to say it. I don't want to say it. So never mind. Yeah, I say
You gave me a hint. So oh sweet. No, I mean you heard it. You heard it say it. So I
Don't know. I'm just like I can't think of a I could be wrong. So I don't want to say it. I could be wrong
I don't want to say anything but who has to pee
But anyway, it was good that she said that I mean that's a good step forward
I think it was and I think like I think you know she kind of like title the stream
Okay, it's a final like last words for me and stuff, but I think we may have ended on a
On a good a good note, you know, I did say can I have a hug and she's like nope
And I said can I have a high five? She said nope
I think I have a little smile and she was okay
Oh, I see, yeah, maybe, maybe, okay, yeah.
She said to you, she said to you what I said
in the beginning, that she doesn't want to involve herself
with the fucking toxic shit that you've surrounded yourself.
All right, it's understandable, it's understandable, 100%.
It's like, you know, like people, like, I don't,
and I don't, gosh, I just, like, I just like,
like to be able to go to different,
I'll even go to like, you know, S-A-M-M-A-N's channel
and stuff like that, but it's like,
Hate it when you do that shit fucking just say the fucking name. We are
I'm not going on there anymore because he's bought too many pairs of Nikes and stuff like
that just from kicking me off the show.
The other day he was playing my content and her content, he played it for literally three
hours and I went up on the panel.
I waited fucking five hours through this horrible shit mumble rap music that he plays.
I was waiting for the panel so I could go up and defend myself.
I go up there for literally like 10 seconds and then I got clapped and that was it.
And I asked for a vest and stuff, and it's like, and then he's like, I don't give a
free vest. Why are you begging him for anything? Why the fuck you begging that scrub for anything?
I'm saying, I want to, I said that would have been nice. Oh, oh my god, person too. Yeah,
person is pretty terrible. No, it's not person, it's not person. Okay, it's a female, maybe.
Yeah, never mind. I could be way off.
Maybe maybe maybe maybe it doesn't matter anyway. It doesn't matter. It's like meaningless
Everybody who is mentioned has always had your back in some way shape or form
Also, it's like I really don't have hate in my heart for anybody and stuff
So, you know, like we had a great night last night page was on the show. We were doing a work with car for car reading
She did some channeling. We had Victoria J on the show
Yeah, get back to basics. I always told you get back to the fucking basics and dude that shit
Yeah
No, I haven't seen tricks today or like, you know last night. I'm kind of getting concerned today
Hey listen man, enjoy the rest of your day. I'll probably pop in later
Take it easy dude. I'm glad you're back with Alexander. That's great. Take care
Well, you know, Victoria, Victoria, no, I'm sorry, I don't think she'd make fun of her man. It's like, you know
I did like when I first I was like, who's this?
You know, but um, but she's been on my actually she came on my show and she's been cool on the show and you know, I
Was able to do cool reading and stuff. So
Hi
Miss Lenore here. Oh
Yeah
So I don't know no person's person is not chill with me person. It always is like and our person also like also
Like portrays like for example, you know my friend Danny or whatever and persons like San Ambedo chef
Well, I went to Danny. I checked out the his final stream and
You weren't there. I
Never claimed I was at his final stream. I've actually said I
Saw his final stream was on my recommended
And it said, you're all fake friends and unsubscribe from me and blah, blah, and I was like, he's in a bad mood.
And so I didn't, I intentionally didn't go, go in.
And so, unfortunately, that was the stream where, you know, she said, she said that.
Well, I don't know I think I heard defend me too
But I think because it's like some people just believe everything in here
So maybe I said things I regret about Victoria J and maybe she said some things without we didn't know each other
We just kind of kind of just people said yeah, so um, but he did that
I don't know first as a male or female, but he's as beat as my always talking shit always about me
Like most of the 90% of the comments I see are just a negative comment about me. So
Yeah, who knows I mean she has like what even interesting picture you look like you know, Sydney Crawford or something in that in that picture
But uh
Yeah, I'd but I'd like to trust people. I like to like open my heart
I like to not have to have suspicion about everybody
I do like sometimes go to the other shows to see
What are people saying about me and it's like are people being too faced and so I see people are saying about me
who's that comes in here and just like is nice to me and stuff and it's like I'm
kind of like had such bad things said that it's like you know it's just kind
of like trust no one I know that's gonna be I have this I used to have this
Illuminati I think I have right here on I don't look it's still on the desk alone
but I have a sticker yeah I do
You like that one?
I hope she is too. I hope she is too. I will remod her
She just she's not really like a like a hider or like she's always like oh, can you mod this person? I'm like Jamie
No
That person is in the psyche haters club Jamie, but I mean I do love Jamie and I hope she's fine, too
I think she's fine
Um, you know
Only the paranoid survive right and it's like sometimes
sometimes
There is a conspiracy or something like that something that's not a conspiracy theory. Sometimes it's conspiracy. I don't know. I've heard things like that
I don't know stay alert stay alive. Hey, what that? Yeah, how about consciousness? That's what consciousness is alertness, right?
That's what consciousness is. It's like awareness of your surroundings and of
motives and potential things. It's part of consciousness. I'm very about consciousness.
Even when I dream, I have consciousness, right? It's like some kind of like another level,
three different level consciousness, maybe more on the astral plane. I did have a great
dream yesterday. It wasn't Nick Johnson, but it was kind of a Nick Johnson lookalike.
He kind of acted like Nick Johnson because he started bringing stuff from the dumpster
He made out with me. He finished on me
It wasn't Nick Johnson, it was a look-alike because I remember like thinking
Oh, I want to show Nick Johnson his picture and the guys like don't take any pictures on me
And I was like what this guy criminal or something and then I
Was like, you know, we you know, he finished on me and I was like, okay. Well have a good day. Bye
And then he just was had like moving in I was like, this is a dream by the way. They finished on me
We made out and then my belly was all wet
True story, I mean this is a dream though by the way guys
Actually, and I didn't it was I didn't finish or anything like I woke up dry, but
He finished on me
It was a great dream one of my best dreams did you have a huge yeah, he did
He did
A friendly new neighbor, he was moving into my bed.
And it was a twin bed.
I was like, are you leaving?
And he was like, no, what am I drinking?
I'm like, I'm drinking ice smash.
It was kind of a nightmare.
What was it?
It was a dream until he wouldn't leave.
And then it turned into a nightmare.
And then I heard him getting phone calls asking about
I'm looking oh, I hear you said you're giving way of TV or something or from the dumpster, and I'm like
I'm like are you giving my phone number to sell?
Junk from the like the street and stuff and he's like oh, yeah, that's my
It wasn't Nick Johnson. It looks just like it might have been Jamie Kennedy for all I know, but it was very strange
The dumpster came into play just because he started bringing stuff
like off the street and stuff into the house and to my it was more like a
dorm room kind of thing it was kind of reminds me of my college dorm room a
little bit the cat okay that's what I was like the cats weren't there and I was
like where are my cats did he sell my cat I was like just confused I was
like what's happening and then I said can you leave and then he and this other
guy were like talking about kidnapping me and then I woke up screaming I woke up
screaming and I was like
I don't know if I was screaming on she because I woke up. I was filming myself on stream at the time
I don't know if I woke up streaming. It was a very it was like, you know
That's why I don't have sex anymore because it's basically like a little minute of ecstasy
And then it turns into a fucking nightmare
Afterwards and they won't leave
You know what the you know, the lesbian brings with the second date a you-haul
Well, I wish I could do the high-pitched woo, but I can't.
Well, well, that's what my high-pitched sound like.
It wasn't a very confusing and erotic dream, but he was, I'll say,
he was a really good kisser. Whoever, whatever this dream.
Have I experienced lucid dreams? Yes, I have.
Actually, I got into lucid dreaming.
I have a book I can show you about lucid dreaming.
I also get to do these recordings and stuff like that.
And also, I learned these relaxation techniques.
You start from your toes.
You lay down, start with your toes,
and you start just focusing on one little part of your body,
going up your body, and your toes start to tingle,
and then your feet start to tingle.
And then show my bookcase.
It's in my other room, but I do have some books around here.
I have like a lot of books here.
These are some of the ones I just brought out.
Like these ones I got mostly go to the library.
Like here's a little stack like this one is like a book of astrology from a library like from the 50s
I got like a big novel of astrology. This one's called meeting the shadow
This is these are some of these I got from the library
It's all meeting the shadow the hidden power of the dark side of human nature
It's a bunch of essays by interesting essays by people this one is the ABCs of the human mind. I
Got these all at the library for a couple bucks
You can program your name when you sleep it's also like you know you listen to student frequencies and stuff
Oh, here's my fucking fire. I got this one on Amazon. This is called this book will change your life
It has like a daily
Exercise or some kind of interesting things every day this one I got from the library
I really like says it's called mythology and in the back of it
It has a pop-up stuff
But this is like a real feather and stuff and has like always pop-up stuff
And then this one is called,
this one I've had for a while.
This is called the only astrology book you'll ever need.
What else do I have?
I have this one right here, how to be an astrologer.
I have this one right here.
This is a really cool art book called the Cartoon Utopia.
And it's just like full of like really fascinating art.
Like it's like very like detailed and trippy and stuff like that and
That's one little pile of books, right? So I think I'm pretty cool books. We're not sleep paralysis. It's called being haggred in
I've had that before too. It's like when like a witch or like it's basically an incubus
Like even most succubuses are just like incubuses. You'll see what else to have
That's my baby album
There's a little pile books if you look at
This one is called interesting stories for curious people. Interestingly, I'm on the cover of this book
There I'm on the cover
for Shamu, I don't know if that Carmen Sandigo or something. I don't know
Balloons and stuff and flat earth and stuff interesting stories for curious people
there is
Oh, the Redondo Beach Library is right on the street.
I have this one called The Illuminati's Trilogy by Robert Chang,
and it's a big, thick, interesting book.
I've read pages from it before.
I have this one I found on the street.
Or I found on there, this little box,
this is buy it, like, give a book or take a book.
This one's called The 39 Clues, the Black Book of Buried Secrets.
But I think it's more of like a, it's really interesting.
It has like cool stuff like the Aster Island guys and stuff.
And this one's called everything you want to know about magic,
but we're afraid to ask.
Kind of interesting introductory book to magic.
It's got a little bit, a little bit basic for me,
but this one's called, I got this from the thing.
This one's called Emperor Picultine Rides the Bus,
an origami yoga book.
I just found this in that little box.
I don't know. It's kind of like interesting because it's like all pictures and stuff and
It has a banana and donuts and stuff. I don't know pretty cool
And then this one's called this book is in a cover, but I'll show you the cover of it
It's called
The book of the horned one a gate of pan magic and there you go
So those are some interesting books I just have on the table right there. I have
this little book cover. Yeah, let me put these back.
Yeah, I got some cool as I mean, and this is just like and I have a bookcase and I have my closet
I have two cloth my two closets are just full of books. Okay. I never I never bought I never had toys
Actually, I went through a faith where I like ninja ninja turtle action figures
And I was like probably ten and I had a few and my brother would like steal them
I also collected like Marvel masterpiece cards and my brother would steal them and like trade them at school and stuff
For Pokemon cards and shit
And I had a bunch of comic books, and then my brother stole it.
Like, he would just like take all my, take all my shit.
Anything that I had was a toy or anything.
Like, he would just steal.
And, uh, but I had books, and he never really stole my books.
Interestingly, my little brother is, like, really successful.
Like, and he, you know, he worked for Netflix, um, doing stuff.
And, um...
He he graduated from the college. I failed out of in the first couple semesters. He lays perks
Yeah, but I so I didn't buy I have toys. I got I got books. I
Love fairy tales when I was a teenager. I like got into like really hardcore into fairy tales
Because I thought they were like I figured out the some
Symbology of them and how they really were for like made for like adults and stuff these fairy tales
Because that was a big fairy, you know.
And, you know, it can I say, a big fairy.
But yeah, most of my books were untouched except for comic books and stuff,
which my brother would steal.
Had my comic book collection right now probably worth a little bit of money
It's like I had a lot of X-Men stuff and I got some rare
I had some rare comic books unfortunately
I like a lot I lost a lot of stuff with it
I had a couple moves where it's kind of like I kind of like left at the seat of my pants had thing and like left a lot
of stuff got left behind
but
You know and I love my little brother too. It's like he's he's gone great out. He's married to a Chinese national
and
you know everyone in my family has a couple kids and stuff or at least you know a few kids and
yeah I like to read I mean I learned how to read but I started learning how to read when I was like
three and stuff you have three books hey you know I'm sure you've read them all though right and
it's like so you know I still have like books to read I have like a lot I have a lot of it's like
a library where it's like there's just so many that it's like it's impossible to read them all but
What's this? I think he's a gay guy and he's like, what is this message?
Yeah, I'm getting a message. It says it's an anonymous message. It says
They said, we're not allowed to comment on your channel anymore, and they said, we'll be targeted if we do.
Wow.
Isn't that interesting?
Isn't that interesting that someone, I don't know who sent that?
Let me look at the state.
Let me look at the area code.
Texas
Someone from Texas. I don't know if it's a bad man. I don't know
It's not like a harassment message as someone from Texas, and I do believe it too. I do believe in spooks
I do I do I do believe in spooks. That's from miserable
You miss the message it says they said we're not allowed to comment on your channel anymore
They said we'll be targeted if we do
So guys, you're brave to be here because I don't want you to be targeted and it's like, you know
I don't want anything negative to have I don't know like it's just sad. I
Would never say no like yesterday I went to I don't know why I keep going over there, but I went to beat us
And they're talking about a bunch of definitions in this guy, Ray or J, no J, the kind of like
these black guy and he's like, Hey, what is, what does this word mean? What is this? What is,
what does innuendo mean? What does projection mean? And so I typed in the chat when he said,
what does projection mean? Cause they were kind of like, they were giving the definition more
of like gaslighting. So he's like, Oh, projection is like, when you say, someone says you're crazy
and you're like, I'm not crazy. And they say, yes, you are. That's, that's not really projection.
Projection is more, I typed in the chat,
projection is when Sandman says it makes fun
of clumsy's teeth, that's all I said,
and I was blocked immediately.
I just have one comment and I was blocked.
You will go where you want?
Yeah, I know.
It's like, were they to tell us anything?
Like, you know what, just be defiant.
Just say fuck you.
who are you my my my mom my caretaker what they're they're gonna target
how about like if you if anybody that fucking messes with my um friends in my chat
i'll target myself fairly fair and square
Maybe a blessing in this kid Tracy Tracy my wise beautiful and Tracy. I am modded everybody. Hey, Tracy
I am modded everybody. So don't think it personal. I just I just I just like you know, I don't really want mods
Like but if you feel like coming up, I do have the link up and I miss you Tracy
I love you Tracy. Just remember guys. It's like I want you guys to just feel
Like you can they don't have to worry about the modding and stuff like that. I have people that I have a couple people
that I have
Helping me and stuff like that with that and I just need a couple people and
I want everyone else to just enjoy and not worry about you're not gonna be hidden. You're not gonna be
Targeted or anything like anybody so it was maybe it is blessing in disguise
You know and I count my blessings, but I love Tracy. I'd love to say hi to Tracy or anybody else who wants to come up
You heard the message the message says they told us not to go to your the comment even comment in the channel
Or we targeted you don't have smoking helps or hinders me to double eyes not quitting, you know
The other night I needed a cigarette like badly
and maybe like a big Mac or something and
Yeah, you don't care about the wrenches. Okay, they the truth you do it. Thank you. Thank you Tracy
I if here's the thing is like, you know, I totally
You know trust you and like the people I had as a mod like trust and stuff
But I just like it's like turns into like people get like I don't want people to be targeted because they're a mod
I don't want people say oh, they're mine here
They're my and it's like I just want people to enjoy themselves and just like you know
I said I have a membership here and if people want to really stand out
They can just pick up a member and it's like you know five bucks a month if they want to I will be putting stuff on members only
A lot of stuff on members only and stuff. Maybe most of my content I will
Yeah, but I love you Tracy. I don't know if you can come up or not, but it's when you know
I love you and I think you're a cool lady, you know
Coolest of my friend my friend that my Russian friend
Also, like, thought you were cool as hell.
Like, when she saw, she was, the first time she came here,
you were on the panel and she's like, wow.
She's like, I love Tracy.
She's like, she's so cool.
She loves like the motorcycle kind of gang stuff.
And like, just like, I don't know
about the Confederate flag stuff, I'm not sure.
But I think she just thought you were cool as hell.
And, you know.
I just don't want people to be upset because I wouldn't get upset when I would when I was a monitor from certain places
I was modern because I was I think it's seriously actually like because I was actually like
It's one emma and another mod there and stuff. I was really really
Promoting her channel support like I was really really out there helping and then it's like I was unmodded because I said something like oh
100,000 subscribers we're gonna have
Diddy baby oil party and that was before like it got there's too much about diddy this a couple years ago
So it wasn't like too much about diddy weed though. You would smoke a fag once in a while when you went out with the gals
Yeah, I like weed
I haven't smoked weed in a while, you know, it's like you guys want anyone's help. I'm saying I'm selling
Some some clap tokens
Won't be saved did most definitely most definitely
100% because I'm like about I'm about eight. I'm around eight and I think he's around I
Mean I mean flaccid. I'm probably about four or five, but he's about one inch flaccid
It looked like a look like a look like a tiny little like a robin's egg and then in a black nest
That's what it looked like. It was like so tiny
Yeah, I'm not thinking too much information and not like the but you know I told I'm a tall skinny white guy like I meant
They're fucking tall skinny white guy, you know
Not at all. Anyway. Yeah, a little Robin's egg. You didn't see it. Yeah, I just saw like a little blue speckled
Something it looked like it was wearing a like a little red sweater and it was covered in black
Hair
Yeah, I don't that's all I can that's the only way I can describe it. I mean, it's like I'm sorry
And like a horse, I mean, it's like seriously, I mean, I like like some Latinos and blacks.
Yeah, it's like a little blue speckled egg, a little robin's egg.
That's all I saw.
I just like it's like, I didn't need to get my like my glasses and like a little microscope.
And I was like, well, oh, there.
Oh, my gosh, there's a little blue speckled egg and a big pubic hair.
Looks like why it was kind of, I think you did have some black, white pubic hair.
Yeah, I zoomed in on it. I was interested
So I was like what I was like I just need to make sure wasn't a vagina
I was like is that a vagina and I like I had to like zoom in. I was like, okay. There's a little bump out there. I
Honestly, Chris the Christine had it right her clit is bigger than his dick
Even her her clit is bigger than his dick
erect. I think he was erect. He tried to do the helicopter. It was more of like
It was more like the motor of this mouse right here.
It's like if you go, you know, this wheel in the mouse, I think it's like that big.
I'm not kidding. I wish I was. I wish it was a joke.
Some people think, oh, he's so funny. I tell the truth, actually.
I'm totally honest. It was like...
In motorboat, no, it was like kind of the wheel of this mouse like there's like it's not even a wheel mouse
It's a laser mouse, but if there was a wheel or I don't know. It's whatever is in there
Like see or see that little on and off button right there. It's kind of like that that big and I'm putting it too close to the screen
But yeah, I
Wish I was kidding. I wish I was I really do and I'm sorry sig I
Just have to be honest, you know
People think I'm I'm like funny sometimes
Like it's like thumb between your fingers if you just like it's making a small like a small like just like the smallest space
You can make like that's how big it was
It's like that I'm sorry my fingers are
Today
Whoa, yeah, he's a speckled cock
Yeah, why would he want us to know that he's a micro that's sad
I think he was like, I don't know.
I don't know why he would do that.
You know, some women do have like a small penis fetish.
Maybe he's looking for those.
Some women like are like, you know,
so like some women are like, oh, you know,
I don't like a big, I don't like to feel it
because they say, oh, a big, you know, thing.
And I feel like I'm being torn apart.
So they want just like a little nub.
They're basically like a like a like a like a maybe like a lesbian
They just want to like something rubbing against the top of their clit without like penetrating them
I think that and that's the sickest perfect for so I think maybe he'll find that kind of woman that was a small penis fetish
They're rare. I
Think they're I mean extremely rare women
But shout out to those women
You know everyone, you know, there's a saying there's a lid for every pot
And even if it's dollhouse furniture, hey,
everyone needs love, everyone, everyone needs love.
He took off the Chastity cage right before he showed it.
Yeah, he had a Chastity belt, right?
The Chastity belt.
Yeah, cause I saw there was a padlock on his underwear.
And I was like, why is he have a padlock on his underwear?
And he had sawed through it.
Yeah.
It's odd through it. I'm not keep shaming. I'm not I'm saying God bless them
It looks like a padlock on it. It looks like a padlock on his underwear. I
Don't know why why there was four but
You're so glad you missed it. Yeah, well, there's there's photographs on my discord of it, you know
Among other but also meanie Manson
with a
microphone on his vagina and his bladder is completely full of like
Gas and pee and he's making this face
I can show you the face hold on
I'm sure the face he's making I can't show anything else in the picture because I'd get in trouble, but there's a face. He's making
See if I can find it I might have blocked the person or I might have archived it. He's making this really disturbing face
Yeah, I think it's might be here. No, I hear
Is it here not here
Here not here
It's here
Here it is. Oh, is that it?
No, that here's a different one of him with the
This is the one where he's holding a razor on his vagina
Okay
It's on my discord I can show you my discord. Let me see. I think it's under my archive
Well, I forgot my art can I go to my archives or archived?
Okay
It's not on that one
Well, I'll just show you the I'll try I wish I could find that photo of the
mini Manson
Making a weird face. I mean I have it, but somebody's discord. I don't I can't show the
Everything I mean I have the picture of this woman like that looks like a turkey
Dude, does anyone know who this woman is?
Someone send me that I
Don't know who that is
See she's a turkey
I think her name is like raw meat ronda or something yeah, no, it's not like a trick
I mean it is like it's like literally a turkey. No, I think Kate knew who it was the Kate's mad at me right now
I hope Kate forgives me and stuff, but
Now I kind of screwed up like I usually do
You're going to jail. This one's going to jail. J-Dog can't save you. Crymorphag. Let me see.
Oh, wait. No, that's the razor blade with the vagina. Oh, is this one? No,
okay. Let's put it over. Are sending me a lot of texts?
I just don't see it.
Here? No.
Hmm.
But look at this one.
Hold on.
Hmm.
He might have deleted that one with the mini mans and stuff, but...
If you go to my Discord, I can send it to you.
Kate's mad at me because she thinks I was S-U-I-C-I-D-E
baiting the other night, because I was like in the chat,
I said something like, I'm going to walk in the ocean.
But I was like, dig it, B, that we're saying I should
walk into the middle of the ocean and stuff.
And then she's mad at me because I said the N-word
the other night.
I was very, very drunk, and I was very emotional.
Aging me on harassing me and stuff and yeah, so she got really mad
But I apologize. I'm sorry. I do like drink too much. I'm just gonna drink these two drinks tonight
And also I was on her I kept trying to go on her show with like this Amanda Erickson photo as a safe puff marshmallow
That's an excuse, but it's like I wasn't basically I was talking about the death of my channel
Okay, not about my actual death. I was I was thinking that my channel be gone any second. I'll give her time. Yeah, I
Yeah
But, you know, she said she's done with me and stuff, so.
But I went on her channel with the Amanda Erickson State Puff
to Amanda, State Puff to Amanda Erickson.
And Q kept saying, oh, John, and I was like, Q, stop.
Everyone knows it's not Amanda Erickson, and it's me.
But you don't keep saying it, you play along, like it's improv and you like talk to me like I'm Amanda and stuff.
That's the funny bit. You don't say, oh John, we know everyone knows it's you.
That is like so lame. He's kind of a younger, he's a 29 or something.
He's kind of like immature and doesn't really understand comedy.
But, I don't know.
I do like hate a lot and I'm like sorry I offended her like again when I said the n-word
I said it like I was screwing it out like a million times
I was drunk and stuff, but it's not it wasn't racial
I'm gonna have to raise the panel age to 30
Why do I have to do that though? Does anybody else?
I might I already have it at 21 and so
If you could, if you roll into drink and, you know, um, pass away for your country and stuff.
You can basically be on a panel on it without a camera on it.
So I don't know.
So I don't have any, it ensures on well, burning joint.
Like I said, like, and this is like, you know, I love Paige and I had Benny on and stuff and Paige and Benny kind of hit it off.
It's okay if they think I'm a sex pass. I'm not it's like it's like okay, so there's this guy named
What is his name? It was like it's like a three these two SSI his name is SSI and I met him on
This good young called the good pussy channel
Well 25 I think it is right isn't it 25 years old and so like
No
Yeah, so they're I mean, it's like but did anybody say and she's I think I don't want to give away her age
I'll say she's maybe in her in her 30s, right?
Other side of the 30s, right?
Nobody has said one
word about that and
That's flirting. I'm not flirting Benny like groomed me like honestly he grooming that he told me like
Told me to start streaming he and it wasn't like a sexual thing. Oh, he's too androgynous kind of for me
But 30 years old what am I gonna do start checking IDs and stuff like that and then it's like oh my god
He talked to a 29 year old
It's not like seriously
Hup, hup.
Where the fake get low and the views dry up
Gotta hate the one crook, he got a sermon half-baked
Say I'm praying for you while these screenshots get saved
Fake are concerned and their boys poison in the cup
Say I hate drama while they winded up got pearls in a death grip
It's a little crisis.
I'm just going to send a real quick text message.
And everything's okay.
Everything's going to be okay.
Everything's okay.
Do you like that one though?
Hey, by the way, yeah, it's right.
I got, I wouldn't make you choose.
I'm like, go wherever you want.
It's a I always try to help everybody in this community. I always try to like go wherever you want. I don't care if you were to stand man. I mean
Hope so
hope so like you know i don't like seeing my friends hurt and it's like you know
some there's some like people that aren't even like on like they're not really streamers and
stuff like that and that are getting bullied and trolled and they don't deserve it and it's like
all i can say is like hey i love you you know why do you care about if you know
You had a break for six months, weeks before I came in the community, then you slowly found
your way here.
Well, I'm glad you did.
And if you're in the haters club, it's okay.
So I love converting the haters club into the psyche lovers club, not in a weird way.
But hey, I don't remember you being anything of a kind to me and that stuff.
And it's a thing is I'm so like, I'm nice to people that are nice to me.
And it's like, but if people get nasty with me, it's not even just me, it's like my inner
Like we can get nasty back. I
Feel bad if they if they go too far, you know like these like protectors I have of mine. I
Hope is averted. I hope it's okay. Just say a prayer for like, you know
people that are like, you know really
get hurt by
some of this
Some of these trolls and it's like and I understand the trolls like
I'm fucking dealing with this for two years like you know pretty much. These are pretty pretty bad for almost like
Some I mean IP two trolls like Benny said himself. They're they're literally trying to like work murder the streamer
And so some people don't don't understand that and they'll say oh well. Why are you saying this and that's like again? It's like
I'm trying to like kind of like bring them out of the just to expose themselves a little bit
Because I believe there's true evil in the world and stuff
I also believe that evil can change to good sometimes, but sometimes there's very little
hope for some people, and it's like, I don't like seeing my friends upset, and I just talk
to somebody very, very, very upset about stuff, and I don't know if it's like targeting hopefully
Especially a really good hard person and good hard people, you know, we open our hearts and it's like in we're sensitive and we're empaths and we're and they know
Hope Christ is a burden. I
Hope so. I'm gonna check something real quick. Just one second
Yeah, I do I do have like some it's okay. You guys can leave like people that are leaving. I see people are leaving and stuff
It's great
if you like basically it's like thinning thinning that they thinning out the
the wolves out of the herd, you came and like stand to listen to like a minute of
you know, music that I put my heart and soul into and just say,
oh you're just lazy, oh you're a suck, you know, blah blah blah, you don't, you don't do,
you're not writing that, you know, you're not, you're not putting any creativity in that,
you're not generating, I don't know, blah blah blah blah. There's some jerks.
Wake up and stretch out, the sun's shining.
I have this thing called the uh
Yeah, um, well q is me. I think it's q
Like the letter q and then panel versus vod. That's trip and sip
I like trip and sip and um, he actually helps me by
syndicating some of that stuff
um
Or syndicating my content and so then I can like kind of delete some stuff and then it's on there
And so I can still like update my codecs and link to it
But here we go
Come to my cabaret. Let's have a cabaret party. I'll be right back
whisper networks and
Concerned little by standards welcome
Please keep your rumors folded neatly under your chairs
We'll be using them as confetti later again
They whispered he's dramatic, unstable, hard to please
Then clutched their pearls so tightly, they near cut off their own breeze
A private little worry here, a solemn little sigh
A bless his heart, I'm nervous with a sparkly alibi
They never tell a whopper when a half-truth will suffice
They serve at room and temperature and call the plating nice
assemble it, they let the crowd infer, then stand there looking in a scent in
beige and cashmere fur. But I know this production, I know each tacky prop, the
script, the cue, the fake concern, the tasteful little slop. You wanted me to
burst on stage and shriek till I was hoarse, instead I crossed one leg and
let you die upon your source. I see the board, I see the game, you sold the scandal,
I sold the name, you wanted Thunderfury.
see the board you find the room arrange the light you prayed i twitch on opening night but now
you're stuck mid-mono
You studied all my buttons like a butler studies wine
You thought my nerves were vending slots that paid out on your time
A jab a glance, a poison joke, a friend with updates twice
You pressed and pressed and pressed and hoped I'd melt for your device
But then I turned to marble with a very decent tan
No jaw clench, no heavy sigh, no let me clear this fam
You searched my face for weakness like a coupon in a drawer
Found nothing but good posture and a gaze that said bored
Through little fox and kitten heels, you curator of spin
You cannot run a puppet show
And no one yanks within a mastermind
A grand machine, a dark, strategic horde
No just one sweaty socialite
And I see the board, I see the board
Then came my favorite counterspell, strategic visibility, no frantic notes, no courtroom
speech, no opera of fragility.
I simply kept on showing up, composed and very real, which is for those who traffic
lies, a deeply rude ordeal.
I smiled at folks, did solid work, behaved with normal grace
And every calm interaction, slap confusion in your face
Because the portrait that you painted wild, unwell absurd
Look flimsy next to me, just being warm and well groomed and heard
Then one by one, without a fuss, I spoke to people plain
Not here's my case, not choose a side, not let me name your stain
Just human voice, direct eye contact, ordinary air
Build your grand alliance on suggestion, fog and vibe
A tiny cult of second hand impressions in a tribe
But lies are cheap upholstery, they split along the seam
Especially when real life walks in better than the meme
And should the room stay rotten, dear, corrupt it to the floor
I do not beg admission to a billed, decoded door
I leave with all my value, all my wit, my work, my spine
And build a bright...
Victim bent and cornered by your art, but all you did was train my eye and sharpen every part
You meant to make me smaller anxious broken underscored
Instead you made me elegant and now
Thank you, darlings. Take your bartender
Distrust the neutral one
Hi guys, well, I'm I don't know something's in the air right now
Like, I just got another message from somebody I'll read.
It's like a friend of mine, he says,
and I don't think I ever tried to do anything weird.
I don't know if he's watching,
I'd love him to join the panel, I'd love him to.
He says, sometimes I wonder if you're a friend or foe.
It's hard to help demons when they constantly seek
to disprove you and warp your intent
to make it look like something other than what it is.
Maybe there's some misunderstanding there.
Why did where does cruel sleep? I think they sleep in trees and stuff
What's inside a cactus isn't it water and what does have it at what temperature does cheese freeze?
It's like a kind of like a stained glass window. It's both like a liquid and a solid. I'm not sure what's up
Dude girls my bro. Yeah, maybe they're underground. I don't know. Did they but like they can like actually like videotape them and stuff
And if you're in your phone, that's a good one
You're coming for me. Well
That's disturbing
Oh, I don't know who said that once they want to come open panel
Who wants to come on panel come on talk to me talk to me come on talk to me
Yeah, I don't know, I try to be a smart ass
and like answer the riddles and stuff.
Cause I think I like to think I'm like
pretty good at riddles and stuff.
But you know what, she puts really good.
Like Alexander the Great went to like a Hindu.
He went to India, right?
And I have this like, hold on a second.
Cactus sometimes does yeah, there's some good cactus I could look up in front of that cactus does sometimes have there's there's some
It's called mess mescaline. I did I did it actually I had mescaline tea in Amsterdam
And you just take a bunch of cactus and you like make a tea out of it. It was really good
They're like hello, how are you doing today? How did you know what's that person?
But when I said something they didn't they didn't respond to me
I'm going to do it. I'm doing fine.
You're never free cheese. Oh, you know what's good is like kind of like the baby, you know the baby bell like those little round in the wax
And then, but they're kind of like good,
more like just like refrigerated, like kind of like,
I used to like my refrigerator,
like put it really on the coldest
and my family used to hate it
because then the milk would start to freeze and stuff.
But I would like go down the middle of the night
when my throat would be all hot
and I'd drink like this like frozen milk
and it's like the best tasting thing.
But they go, stop trying to the temperature freezing
everything in the refrigerator.
But I'd always turn to the highest fucking coldness
that can be, right?
Um, guys, if you want to buy some clap tokens, I'm gonna have them on discount until I sell
five of them.
I'm also gonna throw in a music video for you, um, that we can work on the song together
and the ideas for the video, um, $10 each if you buy two or three tokens.
I will do the music video too.
Also fuck, I'll throw in an astrology report too.
I'll do like an extensive astrology if you want to.
Yeah, this is an idea. I'm just starting out ideas. So I don't know why
And also I'll do the same thing if you buy like there's a cat food like a box of cat food on my
Community wall there's an Amazon wish list with the cat food the tokens are for sale on
cash app or
Venmo and here's the address
And they're good for six months
Kick anybody off the panel, except them, except them, you know, a moderator. So,
you know, so tokens at the peer, but nobody's gonna, we have to be on the show to buy the token,
like nobody on the peer is gonna, I'll say you can sell readings on the peer and stuff,
but um, there, oh, shit, not, there's no two, it's not too, hold on, I'll take the,
it's not too, two Ss, it's just one S, hold on, like so.
I think people would figure that out, but hold on, delete comment.
Bark Barker the queen of 10,000 names Isis. Hey flip-flat. Hey flip-flat. Do I know you? Do I know you from somewhere?
Because you seem to be into esoteric stuff and like really smart and I think I might know you are but I maybe not maybe not
But shout out to you, you're really smart. Let me play you something
I have something called it's one of the best things like in the world like it's like an austic text called
Thunder Perfect Mind and I'll play it for you. It's really just not very long
but it's one of the best kind of like spiritual poems and then because I have
like a little like stuff to check on right now and so I just want to play you
something while I just excuse me for a couple minutes. I'm gonna play this and
because that reminds me a bunch he just posted it's like this really good
Gnostic text called thunder the perfect mind. This is the most powerful spiritual sex ever discovered
It was
It was found in the
Not not a commodity. This is because the not a commodity scripts
Okay, I'll do I'll do a stream at the pier
Guys if I if I make $50 if I get $50 if I sell the tokens
Today I'll go to the pier I'll get fish tacos, and I'll like sit down, and I'll try to do some readings on the pier
Maybe by the the dog is over
Kind of here we go
Just watch this real quick, and if you'd like to I'll check on my cash up in a few minutes, but
I was sent forth from the power, and I have come to those who reflect upon me.
I have been found among those who seek after me.
Look upon me.
You who think of me, and you hears, hear me.
You who are waiting for me, take me to yourselves.
And do not banish me from your sight.
Do not make your voice hate me, nor your hearing.
Do not be ignorant of me anywhere or anytime.
Do not be ignorant of me, for I am the first and the last. I am the honored one and the scorned one.
I am the whore and the holy one. I am the wife and the virgin. I am the mother and the daughter.
I am the members of my mother. I am the barren one and many are her sons. I am she whose wedding
is great and I have not taken a husband. I am the midwife and she who does not bear.
I am the solace of my labor pains, I am the bride and the bridegroom,
and it is my husband who begot me. I am the mother of my father and the sister of my husband,
and he is my offspring. I am the slave of him who prepared me. I am the ruler of my offspring,
but he is the one who begot me before time began, and he is my offspring in due time,
I am the staff of his power in his youth, and he is the rod of my old age, and whatever he
wills happens to me. I am the silence that is incomprehensible, and the idea whose remembrance
is frequent. I am the voice whose sound is manifold, and the word whose appearance is multiple.
I am the utterance of my name. Why? You who hate me, do you love me, and hate those who love me?
confess me and you who confess me deny me you who tell the truth about me lie about me
and you who have lied about me tell the truth about me you who know me be ignorant of me
and those who have not known me let them know me for I am knowledge and ignorance
I am shame and boldness I am shameless I am ashamed I am strength and I am fear
I am war and peace. Give heed to me. I am the one who is disgraced and the great one. Give
heed to my poverty and my wealth. Do not be arrogant to me when I am cast out upon the earth,
for you will find me in those that are to come, and do not look upon me on the dung heap nor go
and do not look upon me when I am cast out among those who are disgraced and in the least places,
nor laugh at me, and do not cast me out among those who are slain in violence.
But I, I am compassionate and I am cruel.
Be on your guard, do not hate my obedience and do not love my self-control.
In my weakness, do not forsake me, and do not be afraid of my power.
For why do you despise my fear and curse my pride?
But I am she who exists in all fears and strength in trembling.
I am she who is weak, and I am well in a pleasant place.
I am senseless and I am wise.
Why have you hated me in your councils?
For I shall be silent among those who are silent,
and I shall appear and speak.
Why then have you hated me, you Greeks?
because I am a barbarian among the barbarians, for I am the wisdom of the Greeks and the knowledge
of the barbarians. I am the judgment of the Greeks and of the barbarians. I am the one whose
image is great in Egypt and the one who has no image among the barbarians. I am the one who has
been hated everywhere and who has been loved everywhere. I am the one whom they call life
I am the one whom they call law, and you have called lawlessness.
I am the one whom you have pursued, and I am the one whom you have seized.
I am the one whom you have scattered, and you have gathered me together.
I am the one before whom you have been ashamed, and you have been shameless to me.
I am she who does not keep festival, and I am she whose festivals are many.
I am godless, and I am the one whose god is great.
I am the one whom you have reflected upon, and you have scorned me.
I am unlearned, and they learn from me.
I am the one that you have despised, and you reflect upon me.
I am the one whom you have hidden from, and you appear to me.
But whenever you hide yourselves, I myself will appear.
For whenever you appear, I myself will hide from you.
Take me from grief, and take me to yourselves from understanding and grief.
and take me to yourselves from places that are ugly and in ruin,
and rob from those which are good even though in ugliness.
Out of shame, take me to yourselves shamelessly,
and out of shamelessness and shame,
up braid my members in yourselves,
and come forward to me,
you who know me and you who know my members,
and establish the great ones among the small first creatures.
and do not despise it because it is small, and it is little,
and do not turn away greatnesses in some parts from the smallnesses,
for the smallnesses are known from the greatnesses.
Why do you curse me and honor me?
You have wounded and you have had mercy.
Do not separate me from the first ones whom you have known.
I know the first ones and those after them know me.
I am the knowledge of my inquiry.
and the finding of those who seek after me, and the command of those who ask of me.
and the power of the powers in my knowledge of the angels,
who have been sent at my word, and of gods in their seasons by my counsel,
and of spirits of every man who exists with me, and of women who dwell within me.
I am the one who is honored, and who is praised, and who is despised scornfully.
I am peace, and war has come because of me, and I am an alien and a citizen.
and the one who has no substance.
Those who are without association with me are ignorant of me, and those who are in my
substance are the ones who know me.
Those who are close to me have been ignorant of me, and those who are far away from me
are the ones who have known me.
On the day when I am close to you.
You are far away from me, and on the day when I am far away from you, I am close to you, I am control and the uncontrollable, I am the union and the dissolution, I am the abiding and I am the dissolution, I am the one below, and they come up to me, I am the judgment and the acquittal, I, I am sinless, and the root of sin derives from me, I am lust in outward appearance,
and interior self-control exists within me. I am the hearing which is attainable to everyone,
and the speech which cannot be grasped. I am a mute who does not speak,
and great is my multitude of words. Hear me in gentleness, and learn of me in roughness.
I am she who cries out, and I am cast forth upon the face of the earth. I prepare the bread and my
I am the one who cries out, and I listen. You who are vanquished, judge those who vanquish you
before they give judgment against you, because the judge and partiality exist in you. If you are
condemned by this one, who will acquit you? Or, if you are acquitted by him, who will be able to
detain you? For what is inside of you is what is outside of you, and the one who fashions you on
and what you see outside of you, you see inside of you. It is visible and it is your garment.
Hear me, you hearers, and learn of my words. You who know me, I am the hearing that is attainable
to everything. I am the speech that cannot be grasped. I am the name of the sound and the sound
of the name. I am the sign of the letter and the designation of the division. Give heed then,
the angels and those who have been sent, and you spirits who have arisen from the dead,
for I am the one who alone exists, and I have no one who will judge me.
For many are the pleasant forms which exist in numerous sins and incontinencies and disgraceful
passions and fleeting pleasures, which men embrace until they become sober and go up to their resting
and they will not die again. Thank you for listening. If these words resonated with you,
subscribe for more journeys into the wisdom of the ages.
Badness.
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream be the callin and slurring words startin up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sykes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob flashing on cam chat losing their mind
Michael getting gong Alex taking flight. It's wild. It's wrong and we do it every night. Hey, he's got him
Synthin hearts in the chat, but she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirting hard let the girls react. It's a freak show party. No filter all facts. Yo
All facts yo
Yo, Michael drops the line gong not tonight
Alex tried a joke, boom, sent into the night.
Panel looking sideways, someone's gotta fight.
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike.
Diamonds feeling spicy, shirts slipping down low.
Oops, she says with a wink, that's the whole show.
Sighs half asleep, but still cracking jokes.
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon, so glow.
No rules, just roles we pretend to play.
One hand on the mute, other letting it spray.
It's a circus, a riot, a beautiful mess.
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob splashing on cam chat losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight
It's wild it's wrong and we do it every night page got them simping hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the girls react
It's a freak show party. No filter all fact
next week you know the vibe
Welcome to the mad
Christine got run over by reindeer on her way back home from feedin' hay.
You can say there's no such thing as bad luck, but we all saw hoof prince and the slave.
She was out there gathering baby goats like some barnyard Santa in disguise with a burlap sack.
Jingle in keys and determination in her eyes
Christine got run over by a reindeer
Trotting fast through moonlit winter mist
Sweet summer yell, girl, move your feet now
But the slay just would not be dismissed
They found her mittens by the mailbox
And a single boot out by the gate
And a note that said Merry Christmas
But it, like the universe, was running late
Some folks laughed and said,
Well, that'll teach ya
Chasing baby goats on Christmas Eve
But sweet summer rolled her eyes and told them
Christine got run over by reindeer
Right beside the holly and the snow
Sweet summer swore she heard him snicker
Like Lady, don't you know the flow
Now the goats are home and feeling smug
Like they planned the whole chaotic scene
Stealing cookies acting like they never heard of Christine
And every year when carolers start singing
We all pause at that one icy bend
Cause nothing says holiday spirit
Like a reindeer with zero respect
But she'd live to tell it mostly fine.
Sweet summer keeps the goats inside now.
And Christine walks a straighter line.
So if you're out there wrangling baby goats,
where the sleigh bells ringing way too near,
hold your snacks, watch your back and stay.
You
I taste the wars I won
Blood on the halo, yeah I move like a loaded gun
Fingerprints of chaos that are up my spine
But you make me righteous with a single crooked line
I cross the wires with the views I know the crime
Every bad direction starts to look divine with you in my sight
Say it all like judgement, carved in bones
Say it like the wood decides what I become
I stand in the flame
I don't dance with the danger
I become a snake
You trace the wreckage but you stand in my way
You see the monsters still call
Like a crown I never thought was mine
Guys, a point for Trix. I hope Trix is okay. I'm calling him outside. He always comes when I call.
Trixie! Trix! Trix!
Here he comes.
A point for Trixie.
another beer. Do I still have a coffee? I still have a whole coffee. I do worry a little bit
because his balls dropped and he's like, you know, he might be out chasing some pussy and stuff
and I don't want him to walk too far and stuff. He just doesn't go very far though.
I hope you like that stuff. I don't know what I suddenly got like 50 people in the chat. I don't
I don't know why, no one's really said anything.
I think I've gotten, since then, I've got 149, 159.
So 10 minutes, no one said one thing, 209 now.
So now it's been 20 minutes into like three comments.
Yeah, Tricks, I don't know.
It's like, he always comes back.
He doesn't go very far usually.
Tricks, Tricks, Tricks!
Tricks!
Trisha's little son like you know, she's getting upset
Your son like and she never liked her kittens. He was like, you know, she like I mean she looked she loved her kittens when they were babies
And then they got a certain
Size and she didn't like she was like get away from me because they have tried to
You're working listening. Yeah, they kept trying to like, you know
Beat off of her and stuff. I know guys. I know my there's like 52 people and they literally no one's talking
And so it's like I think I kind of think I got like a lot of hate watchers
And it's like I don't know I don't want to explain myself over and over again about like I
Never said
I'm sorry if I like maybe use like the wrong language and stuff
I was talking about, like, you ever see the South Park where it's like, it's a
Cartman's Future Grover name, like, it's not Wendy's, it's like some other
Chicagoan South Park. And she, um, yeah, she, um, she quit social media.
And they treated it like a S-U-I-C-I-G-E. Plus I was really drunk and stupid.
That's okay, you don't have to type. I mean, all I'm saying is, like, like, you know,
Like they're making fun of me on Samus.
Oh, you, you're, you're, you're, I'm trying to like do the classic system and nobody's
telling me.
I know that his is more like, I know he's made a lot of money off of like me and built
a new, uh...
I don't know like to build a new wing at the Nike factory from all the fucking. Hey, thank you
I think you guys mean it for for recommending the channel. Hey, what's up hanging our Hong Kong gang people?
Hey guys, if you can just like guys, if you do me a favor
Thanks, first of all, if you get the like button or even hit the dislike if that's still engagement hit the share
Yeah, hit the share
Hi, babe, but you know what, but I was gonna say like Lola like she did come to like love tricks
I know she does love tricks now and they like chase each other around a little bit like oh
You're like that you're like your ears like like that. She meant I just worry a little bit cuz I know like
I'm just very sensitive to the cats emotions and stuff and I just worry and I'm kind of going to worry because I didn't see him yesterday
afternoon and now it's been a
Little while and now he's not coming when I call and stuff and I
Really don't want to check. I mean, I'm gonna start checking like the like next door and stuff like that
There are coyotes in the area. There are
Cars and stuff and I worry
That's my little tricksy. He's ready. He's like the little baby
Yeah, are you okay? And now she's acting worried and so I get worried
Acting a little bit worried, huh? Where's tricks? Where's tricks? Oh
See, I don't know and I'm gonna worry cuz she's kind of like you see she's kind of like a
Little like worried
Because he's his mama
The other kid in like they kind of like left so early. She's kind of like, oh, you know
Yeah, Victoria was here last night. Victoria was here last night. She came on panel and stuff Victoria's cool
Guys want to do I'll do readings right now
I'm selling I'm selling the clap tokens if you want to do other stuff. I
I'll train you in AI. I mean I mean guys. I'm like really
I have a lot to offer and I'm just trying to present it the right way without trying
to seem like, oh, I'm just trying to get McDonald's and stuff.
Cool?
Yeah.
I think she's cool.
She's like judge people.
Are they respectful to me?
Are they, do they come on the panel and talk and like,
are they rude to me on the panel?
Do they talk shit about me elsewhere?
I never really saw her talk shit about me and stuff.
If you wanna do a reading, I can put the cash up link
and stuff, cause I'll do free readings.
It's free three card.
If you can become a member,
I'll do like a 10 card reading for you and stuff.
You know, if you, I mean, whatever you wanna do,
if you wanna buy like the cat food and tell me,
You know, I mean all kinds of stuff. I have a lot to offer is a thing. I'm not like
Just sitting here trying to like get drunk and like
You know, maybe I will buy a couple more drinks tonight if I can but
I'm not sitting here trying to like sit. Oh, I'm not ready. I'm not a grifter. I'm not a scammer
I have a lot to offer. I will make whatever you want to do
I'll make it worth it if I don't you know, I'm I've no problem refunding and stuff, but I mean I'm just been so slandered and so like you know I
Hey, babe
You're upset are you upset are you upset or something?
Yeah, oh she's biting my nose and stuff kind of just concerns me a little bit
So just a prayer for tricks
Fire sales, I don't have the fire sale set up yet
Victoria's room the real ones, so I'm not a beatbox streamer
Well, are you talking about that little alcohol beatboxes and stuff? I do like those and stuff, but no, I'm not like trying to like
By depart. I'm more like a Mike's harder lemonade kind of streamer, right? You want one too?
Like a hard limit I know I know I know
Guys, you can type exhalation by butthole,
exhalation by plug, see what happens.
Try that.
Those are set up.
Part of what I want to do is I want to,
I do want to update the codex.
Like most of them, like a lot of the money I make,
not most of the money, but a lot of the money I make
goes to like paying for this like,
intelligence that scrapes my transcripts and and just like helps do the codex and
stuff because it's like not perfect right now I'm gonna start make sure I have
the have everything available all the videos available on it at least even for
members and stuff I spent a lot of I spent like six months trying to do this
It could be several hanging on a honky.
Yeah, it's kind of like the hennie-pennie,
or who is that, there's like a story.
And this chicken wants to make some bread, right?
As the chicken's like,
hey, can you, can I get the chicken and borrow an egg?
And like no one, no one would lend you an egg.
Can I borrow some flour?
No one's gonna borrow the flour.
Can you help me need the dough?
No one helped her need the dough.
Like, no one helps her do anything.
She had to do everything herself.
And then she makes the bread.
And then everyone comes to eat the bread.
And she's like, you know what?
She's like, I bought the eggs.
I bought the flour.
I needed a dough.
I did everything.
And so I'm gonna eat this fucking bread myself.
And that's what happened.
Hi, baby.
Nice to meet you.
It's a good story.
It's a good fairy tale.
Oh, hi, babe.
See, she's a little bit, I don't think it's like,
She's like didn't see something bad or like acting like this because
Something bad happened. I hope it's like because
She's just worried like I am
Are you just worried like I am because where's your worst tricks he's always here, right?
Where's your son?
It's her last child. It's the tricks stayed with the
crew
and she came to love him because she didn't like her.
Oh, except you wanted to chat.
Thanks for coming in.
And no one's coming on panel and no one's really,
there's some people chatting and stuff.
Thanks for being here.
Stone Soup.
Oh, Stone Soup is a great book too.
It's like a stone.
It's like an Italian folk tale or something like that.
And that's like, they make, or they put the stone in
and it's like, and they put all those other ingredients in.
And but the stone is like the secret ingredient of it, right?
That'd be good IRL content to record or a good thing you gotta go. Okay. Go hang out with Trent. Okay. Thank you
I think you're being here. Is it Trent Reznor? Hey, do you want to be more? Can I wear you like my scarf and wear you like a scarf?
Okay, okay, okay, I'm sorry too far happen with Trent, okay
But thank you for coming by I appreciate it. Hey everybody 670 people here
Have Maya and her friend are talking but nobody else is talking like really nobody else is talking and I don't bought my chat guys
It's trend is Canadian. Okay trend the Canadian. Oh another Canadian. Hey, well, hey
Hey, nice to see you subscribe to the channel
Stone soup. Well, do you want me to make a stone soup or do you it's called a cult of psyche?
I'm called or trends or trend has a channel. Yeah
Well, let me know I'll post this channel and stuff as a thank you for stopping by
I'm happy to promote anybody. What's the recipe?
It's like a stone and some and some water right and then you put in carrots and you put in some like broth and you put
In some vegetables and it's like but the stone is a secret ingredient. It does not require a spider to be flush in the toilet
No flashing I'm all about flashing
And I don't I meant I'm not like the fucking hottest guy why the stone because it's I'll read the story
I'm gonna read the story for content. Okay, babe. I'm gonna read the story of the stone soup
And it's been probably like probably literally like like 40 years since I read it
I probably remember like five years old, right?
But I remember I think they have a stone soup and like the stone was like the secret ingredient and stuff, but it was like
really like not that important
because it was like all the other ingredients,
but it was the stone.
I don't remember exactly.
That's why I have to look it up.
I kind of am a mythology fairy tale story.
Do you ever hear of like the Nanna,
what's it called?
It's like Nanna Yona or something like that.
And there's like an Italian thing
and there's like the spaghetti.
She makes this pasta and the pasta starts coming out of the,
pasta starts coming out of the bowl
and it takes over the whole city.
Yeah, stone soup, you have to have the stone,
but then it's like all the other ingredients
that really do it, but the stone,
because the stone doesn't have any taste or anything,
unless it has some really good dirt around it.
Okay, let me, I'll read the story to you guys.
Okay.
Here's the story of the stone soup.
Here's the story.
A long time ago,
A long time ago, in a village, not too far from a stream, a kindhearted soldier was trudging
down a dusty lane.
His movements were slow as he had been walking the whole day.
He would have loved nothing more than to eat a nice hot meal.
As he came across a quaint little house on the side of the road, he thought to himself,
that person who lives here must have some extra food to share with a hungry traveler,
And so the soldier walked up the cobbled path toward the wooden door, past the garden full
of growing cabbages, potatoes, onions, and carrots.
Once he reached the front of the house, he raised his hand to knock when the door suddenly
opened.
On the other side stood an old man.
His hands were on his hips and he had a frown on his face.
What do you want? said the old man, rudely, still the soldier smiled at him.
Hello there, I'm a soldier from a village not too far from here.
I have come to ask you if you have any food you would be able to spare.
The old man looked at the soldier up and down and replied very bluntly, No, now go away.
The soldier was not put off by this he smiled once again and nodded his head. I see I'm only
Asking so I will have a few more ingredients for my stone soup
But I guess I will have to have a plane just a tasty thought
The old man scrunch up his eyebrows stone soup. Yes
No, I'm not banned from the library. I'm a secret library. No, I was banned from a library because my dad would drop me off there to read books
I would read the books the librarian thought my dad was like dropping me out there for them to be babysitters
And like they're like stop dropping your son off at the library. We're not baby sitters here
This whole label this whole librarian and also I mean seriously. This is a true story. Okay
Is it so the man thing? No, no go away
The soldier was not put off by okay, so he says
Well, yes, sir
Now, if you'll excuse me, and he starts walking away, the soldier walked to the middle of
the path and hauled an iron cauldron from his belongings.
Once he had filled it with water, he began to build a fire under it.
Then, with great ceremony, he drew on ordinary-looking stone from a silk bag and gently dropped
it in the water.
The old man watched all this from his window bewildered.
And after a while of washing the soldier at the water,
I stir the water with a small stick,
the old man walked out and asked the soldier,
what are you doing?
The soldier took a sniff of the steam coming out of the pot
and licked his lips in anticipation.
There's nothing I like more than a tasty bit of stone soup.
Then he looked at the old man, adding, of course,
stone soup with a little bit of salt and pepper
is hard to beat.
Perfect.
Here we go. Perfect, cried the soldier as he sprinkled them into the pot.
Hold on. It has no hesitantly the old man went inside and returned with salt and pepper,
slowly handing it over to the soldier. Perfect, cried the soldier as he sprinkled it into the pot.
He stirred it once more before looking over to the old man again.
But you know, I once tasted this amazing stone soup with some cabbage.
Oh how wonderful, the old man approached the cabbage plants and picked the ripest cabbage
handing to the soldier.
Oh how wonderful the soldier exclaimed as he chopped the cabbage up and dropped it in
the soup.
He took a deep snip of the pot and said to the old man, you know, this would be a soup
fit for a king with a few carrots.
The old man said thoughtfully, I think I can find some carrots, then he went over to his
And so it went on.
The old man began to grow delighted with the smell
from the pot and brought onions, potatoes, and beef,
and so on.
The soldier himself also added things like mushrooms
and barley from his own bag
until he declared the soup was ready.
The old man smiled as a soldier,
the soldier when he offered half the soup to him.
Why don't you come inside? I have some fresh bread brought strip in the bakery this morning
Yeah, what's his delicious with the stone soup?
He said kindly and the old man and the soldier shared a wonderful meal together
The soldier brought out a carton of milk from his bag and together they shared that too the old man
Meaning chills. Why am I getting chills up into my body? I'm sorry the old man agreed
that
With the soldier with the soldier that the soup is he said better than anything they had ever tasted
Before it wasn't until the soldier had given him the silk bag containing the stone
That the old man realized the truth
It was never the stone that it created the delicious soup rather by working together
I'm getting chills. Why am I getting like chills? Okay? I'm sorry by working together
And being generous, both he and the soldier
had been able to create a scrumptious meal
they could share between them.
I hope you like that.
Thank you for recommending that story.
That's a beautiful story.
And it's like, sometimes we're like,
oh, I don't wanna share what I have with you
because this is mine and you can't do anything with this.
But it's like, sometimes when we work together,
and we can each provide something the other needs
and it's like we have more.
Isn't that a good story?
That is a fucking good story.
I know them, I get it, I just get it.
And thank you for recommending it.
I haven't remembered that, I didn't really remember.
I just remember there was a stone soup
and the stone wasn't really the point of the soup
because the stone is like nothing,
but it's like the old man like share everything.
It's really cool.
I bet he'll be back.
I bet he'll be back very soon.
Yeah.
But people think I'm like, oh, I'm just trying to grift,
and I'm trying to.
And that soldier was a little bit of a grifter
in a certain way, because he kind of tricked the old man.
But at the same time, he provided what he had, too.
And he had more than the old man thought the old man didn't know he the old man
Just thought he had a stone maybe and was like
But then he had milk he had barley he had herbs and stuff and they're able together to create it
I don't know. I'm not gonna go too far into it. You guys get it. You're smart
It's okay, Lola
He was a grifter, he worked it, but also like a grifter is kind of like, I mean, a grifter
I kind of think more of like a con artist that is just like going to do the pure trick.
The soldier was actually, first he was a soldier, so that's kind of like brave and stuff.
And second of all, he did have stuff to offer that the old man didn't, wouldn't know.
But he also had this intelligence, you know, to be able to like, you know, share that.
Hey, oh my gosh, I want to thank I think somebody bought some tokens. I'm not gonna give the
name
Okay, let me just look at the thing
Okay
You love the tattoo, okay, I'm not gonna give the name but they love the tattoo and that was a little thank you for the tattoo
Thank you
Thank you. I love the tattoo too
Also, and I'm gonna give you I'm gonna show you to you again because you aren't generous and kind person and I appreciate that, okay?
There you go, I
Think it was a perfect tattoo
You know how to get it like you show people they had more than they had
No, no, yeah, and the old man was like I have like a vegetable garden
I can maybe chop some carrots with a bread for dinner, and I'll have some carrots. Oh
You guys should elect your look I got it fixed
I got it fixed.
Gals on the Christine streamer.
Did you have one today?
Christine, you know, Spunky Spunky sponsored the tattoo.
No, I don't care.
Cause it says what I wanted to say.
It says what I wanted to say
because it was a marker of shame before an embarrassment
and now it's a mark of defiance and honor.
And I think it's perfect.
With that on I was gonna have it. I was gonna have a cover with the make it Lenore and stuff, but I'd rather have that
Thank you. Isn't that cool? Yeah, spunky. Um, if you know spunky, she's really really cool
No, it's not fuck cat because I have my own it's like fuck it's like fuck that gang
Which is very little to do with cats like their gang is like about like I don't know what they're they're gangs about
But I just had it all wrong
But I have a cat gang
I have a cat gang. I have a duck gang. I mean, I say, I mean, I'm, I'm fully satisfied. I mean, it's like, it's just perfect.
Isn't she cool? Yeah, she was on the other day. She had been gone for a few months and I was like, I just mentioned to her in passing. I was like, yeah, like, you had a good idea.
He said, yeah, I'm in the Quackers. If you're to the Quackers, I'm in the Quacker gang.
And, you know, Alexander McQueen, Easy, Les, there's a few people in that that are really
cool guys.
And when I needed them the other day, hey Aldi, when I needed them, when I needed some people
the other day because I was having a rough day, they, I just heard quack, quack, quack.
I just thought all this quacking and all of a sudden all these people appeared in my stream
Hey, what's up clumsy?
Hi, hey papa all these cool all do I come up and say hi guys. I think the link pinned
If not, I'm kind of having a little bit of like a little bit of a rough day cuz tricks hasn't been around
But I'm like now I'm like really worried about him and that's gonna be in the back of my mind
It's not hell Billy's gang hell Billy has the let's scam psyche gig cuz hell Billy kept saying I'm gonna send you the
garbage pill kids tarot deck
And he's like, I sent it, it's in the mail.
And he's like, oh, I sent it.
And then I asked my wife to send it, blah, blah, blah.
He never sent the deck.
His wife never sent the deck.
He has ducks, well, they escape from his hell.
Hey, Rudy, I never, I don't have the garbage pail
kids care or deck, which he promised me.
and said he had sent, and yeah.
So her ability is a scammer.
He's a scammer.
And then I heard him on Beeta's talking shit about me
just the other day.
Beeta, oh my God, that socky, you know.
Yeah.
She did?
That's cool flip, flat.
This monkey has a good heart.
She has a really good heart.
And sort of like a lot of people, like a lot of people here.
And it's like, I'm also upset
because I've had a few friends contact me today
Well, these people are doing this to me and that, and it's like, you know, and they, you know, there's like a song that was like, you know, a negative song, like, hey, listen, I got negative songs, too.
And it's like, I was like, let's write it. Let's write it. Let's write a better song. You write a better song, better quality and more true than what these people, these people actually just throw something into the air.
And so, you know, I don't know.
You're gaping open daddy.
What?
Aldi? Is that Aldi?
You're gaping? What does that mean?
It's a little bit much.
It's the real Aldi guys. It's a real Aldi Aldi get up here
Get up here Aldi. You're cute. You're cute
She's like your other cheeks better. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I said too much I
Always go a little bit too far. I do go too far. I have to say oh my gosh. I am so sorry
How awkward awkward it might be it. That's why I'm asking come on the panel then I'll know for sure
It's my it's my cute Aldi
My chubby cheeks
One time he was blonde and then I was like can I see your hair and then he showed me his pubic hair
And I had to end the stream
And he has big balls
He does have big balls, but kind of like sick I
Also, I do want to share this video
I have it on private right now, but I just feel like this is the right time to show it again
That feel like I
Just feel good about playing it right now
Okay, I meant I'm actually a good good state of mind to play it. I'll be right back gonna put this video on
it refines my mirror eyes they don't flinch in the storm they just watch the illusions form
i cut through the nerves which planes mid-flight bleeding truth in the glare of the light now
i'm electric wide open alive didn't gauge the feeling let it thrive watch me ascend while i'm
and sing shout out!
Blessing the dark, praising the blue
The light is the canvas, where visions move
My voice cracks under, my veins rumble
Hold me close, I'm becoming new
I come to the core, I switch into grace
I've lived this world for my own mistakes
Now I'm full, no mask, no wall
Didn't contain the feeling at all
Watch me ascend while I'm shit
Eyes closed, I fell through cosmic time
Madness and magic, you're pulsing mine
Circle divine, our souls in blind
You're tied to me, but I choose the line
I cut you free
Born in the hush before the sun, between two worlds, the day they come.
Twitty, a rising silver spun, a vow was whispered, he is the one.
Utara, Shadha lit your skin, Shravana, I flowed from within.
A victor's crown you didn't win, you were the storm they ushered in.
Winter hot, get wild grown, a wild child made of steel and stone, with shadows crawling, take your throne.
from distance star, a voice that splits the lies apart.
You are the storm-born architect, the truth they fear,
the soul they wreck, the map of God's inhuman flesh.
A myth they tried but failed to check.
You rise from worlds that came before.
A judge is sage, a hidden war.
You break the law.
in trail, your voice, the lightning in the gale.
every slander into tide reverses lies they try to hide your enemies now choke on
pride you are the storm-born architect the truth they fear the soul they wreck the
map of gods in human flesh a myth they tried but failed to check your eyes
from where
digital age with memes and trolls as war and stay you wield your voice like
sharpen blade a neon wrath psychic mage you
That's what you came here for.
I lost the right people though.
It's like, you know, kind of like sometimes I don't,
like, I'm really son of a,
if I cared about viewers,
I would have like my videos monetized exactly for,
but I lost people that were like,
oh my God, AI music.
And they sit there listening to like hours
of mumble rap on Siemens channel
or whatever his fucking name is, who cares?
They're good, good.
I hope they go.
The real ones are still here.
I'm listening to the literally
fucking, fucking, fucking, fucking, fucking,
anywhere, anywhere, anywhere.
And people are seeing there for hours.
Oh, we didn't say he's clip coming up.
I can't wait to see it.
They don't come and watch my clip on my show.
They don't watch me, but they want to see me on that show.
Or, you know, it's...
It's confusing to me, it's like sad, I'm like,
let's watch my show and stuff and like,
you can see it all, you can see the speedo,
you can see everything you wanna see here.
Or you can go watch their edited clips
to make me look as bad as possible.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
I don't know, you can just watch my show.
Someone threw me a few bucks because they like my tattoo
You know, I'm a blessed person. Let me just say I'm blessed
I live in a beautiful city. I have beautiful cats. I have beautiful true friends
I have everything I can want
Okay, I
Don't care if like more people hate me they hate me. They just don't know me
if they knew me they'd probably like me they really knew me even the people that hate me more are like
well i do like him and stuff i think he's like pretty intelligent person pretty talented in a
certain way you know but if they don't they just don't get it i feel sorry for them they
Yeah, I'm gonna play this song
This is called curious away
I can't see my dolls cup is in the way. This is called curious away one of my favorite songs
You taught me what power was.
By showing me everything you were willing to betray for it.
the floor your heat still poisons the air that I breathe I don't believe in friendship anymore
daggers in my core your mask to burn the trust underneath I won't mistake these snakes for love anymore
It's my cold
But CO2 is the only truth we've got.
and you personalize pretty much everything.
It's my own trauma.
I'm not a perfect person.
There's many things I wish I didn't do.
But I continue learning.
And here is what I have to say to you.
Just one thing more to say before I go.
So many here I need food. I have a fucking pool bag of McDonald's fries
I have Alice gonna come on Alexander McQueen's gonna come on and he said the rest of the week I get free McDonald's
So I'm pretty much fed. Hey, Samman. Are my arms bigger than yours? Can I challenge you to a wrestling match?
Nuka I said Nuka knucklehead knucklehead
See these snakes?
I have these twin snakes called Kundalini.
Or my arms.
They're gonna go, psst.
Okay, well, I'll enjoy it.
Here's where I'm gonna enjoy more,
kicking you out of the chat.
Bye, Nuka.
Bye. Oh, my gosh.
No one even cares what her witty said.
Oh, my God, I hit Loki.
Loki, it was an accident. It was an accident.
Sam, Samman is banned.
How embarrassing.
And then Chad is going too fast.
Here, lookie, lookie, I got you, lookie.
I'm gonna get you back home.
You got, I got, I'm sorry.
I'm a little bit drunk.
Guys, I don't have a mod to it.
Okay, I'll do it myself.
And then I have a really cool swimming to show you.
It was an accident, lookie.
It was an accident.
I tried to do it the same way.
I'm gonna find it.
Where is it?
There we go
Gluke you're back you're back
There's the tears of five-minute band anyway, but yeah, you're back. I
Know you got friendly fire. You got friendly night, but you're back in ten seconds. Hey McQueen's here. What's up McQueen?
You got friendly fire
There you go guys respect Alex and
Felipe
Got a couple good mods here
Guys I see a prayer. I haven't seen tricks today. I've been calling him. He's not coming back and stuff
It was up Alex
Sam has been he find me saying oh, you know, you're not gonna have McDonald's for the
You're not gonna eat and stuff like hey
He's such a bitch
Hey, we have a guest. Oh my gosh, the big up. It's the big up guys. Let's guys now you're gonna regret guys
You can still but I just want to say
while you can get them
$10 clap tokens and
mods
Alex you if you have a like five free tokens by the way, I was in a McQueen
I was under mayors you get you get them five free clap tokens
Jimmy's Cowboys does, Joni does, and Felipe does.
Enjoy, enjoy.
Enjoy what?
I will.
What am I going to enjoy?
That nuka?
Enjoy what?
Does that what he had to say?
Clap tokens are you can you can kick anybody off the panel you want
I and all my the only thing I'm on which this is like a it's like a big thing of um, of uh, like uh
Wet cat food
Isn't he weak isn't he just like lame is that the best thing you can say he could have said anything he wanted right there
That's all you have to say
That's the face he makes literally
Same as
Pretty much like even people there are just there to laugh at you. I mean it's like even at least here
I have real people here real ones
I know you can bike you guys you kick about I want to bring up for 24 hours if you want to buy them
Well, isn't that amazing? I mean he's just like laying it's like of all the things you can say
Embarrassing that was embarrassing Sam and
That was not a W, that was an L on your forehead.
Are you laughing, what, you're laughing, Nicole?
I know, Samet, do you ever have people laugh so hard
that they use that emoji?
I've never seen that emoji in your chat, ever.
They're like laughing so hard they're crying.
That's what I can do.
Here's what you can do.
Oh, I, I, this is an hour and a half more of music, okay?
Just two more. It's only going to take another three hours
and we can watch Big Troll do her makeup.
I don't want to look like Big Troll.
She doesn't do her makeup right.
I mean, I don't have anything negative to say about her, really,
but she's not the best makeup artist.
I mean, why do you have, like, a channel dedicated to Big Troll?
Doing her lip liner and she does her lip liner a little crooked her eyeshadows off like it's not
Then that's all you show and then and then my my show
No one care like really why are people watching that show
Why are people I don't understand I think it's because it's like they're like tired and it's like they want to fall asleep or something
To like nonsense
It's a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a
Oh, guys, let's watch another 5 hours of BigTroller doing her lipstick liner.
Huh?
Shalilulu!
Really, Samman?
Really?
I mean, I think...
Hey!
No, you're not. No. Don't even try to play it. You're gonna lose. We already know. We already know you're not smarter than the fifth grid.
We know you're not smarter than a kindergartner. A kindergartner and special ed, not no shade of special ed people will win trivia to say a man.
Like, I'm not even kidding. I wish I was just joking. The funny thing is, here's why people laugh when I talk.
I just tell the truth, and the truth is sometimes funny and strange and weird, but I tell the truth.
They're laughing at you because you're retarded, like literally retarded.
And they're mean, and I don't even laugh at you for that. I just laugh at you because it's like, I don't know.
I'm glad, I don't want you to be evicted from your apartment, Sandman.
I know you're like the breadwinner of the household, okay?
The poor broom is gonna be sweeping the alleys
without you staying in that apartment.
You just need to.
I know.
You want some cat flea colors?
I'll put some cat, like they really don't have that many.
Do you get a couple fleas?
But I don't see one.
I don't see one.
A little, do you get me any fleas?
No.
And she was an alley cat.
But I'll put I'll put them on there four colors. I'll put some flea collars on the Amazon. Well, we'll be right there
And I'll put I'll get because it's like if you guys
Are concerned about the fleas and stuff
Yeah, they do pick up some a couple fleas. I really get a combing them and like getting them all off, but I
Look at flea collars for cats cat flea collars
You guys when I help the cats out
Guys how about like we get a year supply of food for the cats and stuff like seriously first thing
I did today when I woke up was walk to Petco and get plenty. You know the cats are so well fed and stuff, but
You know
They can use it. Oh, I have it. I do have something for the cats though. I do a good thing especially for you though today
Oh, no fighting no fighting with Marie
What do you get? Are you guys here? Are you guys here?
Are we gonna have a party?
What did I get? I got a big bag of these things called natural yums
It's a natural yums. Hey Nancy, how are you sweetheart? Where's old man Rudy? This is Rudy right there. That's Rudy right here
Rudy do you want it? You want some natural yums? What do they have catnip on them vitamins and minerals?
Catnip flavor. You got the catnip flavored yums
Let's see if you get high on these. Oh, Lenore's over here too. Lenore's at Rudy's butt. Lenore. You got some yums too, Lenore.
You woke up? Lenore suddenly woke up from her nap. Okay, you got some yums too here. There's some yums for you.
You want some Lola? Come here. Lola, yum's for you. You got some yum's, too.
Lola, come here. Lola. Lola.
Some yum's coming.
It drops on the floor, so she's getting the floor full.
Give him a feed of, look at it. There she is. And here's Lola having the yum's.
They're all having yum's.
Oh, Rudy likes these. Look at Rudy's crunching on them.
and Lola, and so is Lenore.
Yeah, if you buy the case, there you go, guys.
No fighting over them to get kind of high sometime
on the cat hip and they start to fight a little bit sometimes.
Like now Lenore's rising up.
You like the yums?
Is Lola having them too?
Tricks, I'm gonna shake my hands and do it
because Tricks hasn't been back today.
A little bit concerned, but Lola's having them too.
Oh shit.
Lolo, you're having a yum stew?
I'm going to shake it once I have the window for tricks, huh?
I'll put the yum stew in here.
But there's a Miss Lola having to...
See you soon.
Enjoy, enjoy.
Trixie, Trix, Trix.
Trixie, yum.
Yum yum.
Trix.
I got some yums, I got some yums today.
I got some nom-nomes.
You like that?
You're like, here, here, I'm going over here.
Well, hey, I'm getting some messages, hold on.
I hope Dricks is okay too, I worry about him.
He like, you know, he's a guy, you know,
he's probably in his teenage years and stuff.
He's like, probably a little bit horny sometimes.
No, it's not supposed to it's made of wood. It's white because it has some little bit of ash on it and stuff, but
It's not terrible
There's some more here. No, come here
Easy
Yeah, that's a little bit ash that has a little bit of tobacco ash on it. I'm gonna put up the link again and guys
Or someone in this house that he put up a comment and said there's look a little nor looking the mark
Yeah, he's like, oh someone said oh well you're like getting
You're you just you you sell claps, but you don't get in me now. I'm actually like doing like
Like if you if I swear say them we'll be back within like like an hour especially after this and it's like he's made
Probably $200
Just in me being clapped over a show. Oh my gosh. Do you like these?
And then he's like then be didn't him or just laugh again me saying oh nobody cares about you ever
We're just kids about Sam and Sam and a beta and they're like a Disneyland beta looks like you know
She looks like what is it look like?
She looks like Shrek a little bit like Shrek with like a black wig
And this writing Samann is so AI'd,
where he looks like a good looking person,
where she's not.
He's not.
Ever see Samann's real picture?
It's like,
it's like Shrek looks like Fiona
and Bita looks like Shrek,
which is weird, but okay.
So, no, you're sitting in front of the camera.
No.
I think we're already eating.
He likes those
Yes, he was you know, here's the first a beta said I said Samman
Because he was playing commercials and stuff like on the um on the thing I was like Samman
take some of the clap money you get from me and
Buy YouTube light premium. It's cost literally seven dollars a month. You don't see a commercial. I guess I get YouTube light premium
And BD goes, Samman, oh, he's saying that you have a clapping system, and he has one too.
And so, bitch, bitch, please.
She was laughing at me, low key.
I know you're like her, and like I said, would I ever say low key, don't go over there or
anything?
You know, McQueen and Felipe's a mod and I have a few others that are anonymous, right?
Ruby likes this shit. You like the catnip? He likes the catnip treats. You like that?
But Pita said that and then he's like, oh, I can sell a clap token.
Share the link? Oh, someone says share the link? I don't know if you do.
You like these already?
I know, we're having fun.
Literally, I'm over there.
I'm like, I just want to walk through
and see what's going on.
Cause there was like a hundred,
I was like, there must be something going on.
There's literally a black screen with like pebs talking
or something like that.
Cause I love pebs, but like, it was like,
literally nothing going on.
I was like, what's going on here?
I was like, why are people over here?
And then he's like, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, urrr, ur
It's like training for them.
Hey, man, how are you?
But anyway, you want some more?
The tricks doesn't come in.
That's what I'm really concerned about.
Here, baby, yeah, pretty good enough here.
You can have some more.
The tricks doesn't come home.
I'm worried too.
A chatter's asking, no, the tricks doesn't come home yet.
And I've been calling him
and he's been on these things for a long time too.
You know, and I do worry.
I think Trix is just out getting some pussy.
He always comes back smelling like cigars and whiskey
and stuff, here you go, here you go babe.
And it's like, I think he either goes to like
some old lady's house where she like keeps him inside
and stuff and like he has to like break out.
I haven't seen him since yesterday.
I haven't seen him since probably like yesterday evening.
So I am concerned, but he's obviously stays out that long.
And he comes home and he, he like, yeah.
No, not, and then there were two.
And you're also banned for staying and something like that.
What's happening?
Good to see you, chicken cakes.
We're just hanging out.
And it's banning the people that are just like being horrible.
I'm worried about my cat.
Can I, can I?
Okay, we have a guess.
Oh, we have a guess.
Was it, I haven't seen him probably since last night.
We have a guest all the way from the beautiful
region of Canada.
I think Canada, he does the best Christine imitation
I've ever heard.
He does the best Sweepy imitation I've ever heard.
He does the best Beatty imitation I've ever heard.
You like farts?
Well, I know you do Canada dry.
Well, why don't you suck on them and get high on them?
Okay, you're just asking Nuka.
No, so people on us sweepies at you. I'm sorry man
Sweepie is that you I can't do that anymore. Oh get out of here though. I don't want to talk to you
It's called
improvisation
You're not supposed to say oh, I can't do that imitation. I wanted to hear sleepy and then you just ruined it by like, you know
Arthur
So disappointed in you, and why haven't I gotten your wrestling video yet? You said you were wearing Speedos
You haven't sent it to me. I'm not gonna let you back on Arthur until you send me a wrestling video
Okay, okay, okay Arthur and literally until I see you in your Speedos
I do.
I like sweeping.
So do you.
Can I cry?
Even though you.
Yeah.
Can I cry?
Even though you struck her channel?
I know you did.
Arthur, you're not coming back until you send me a link to your wrestling video.
You know, keep her in private chat.
I won't share anything.
I just went up for private masturbation purposes.
And if you don't want to set it.
Okay.
Hold on.
One second.
Okay.
Okay. Well, you're banned. You're banned forever. Hold on. Is that Sweepie? I think I hear Sweepie coming.
I think I hear Sweepie in the back. Sweepie, is that you? Okay. No, no. He ruined it again.
Never mind. Never mind. It's over. It's over between you and me, Arthur.
It's over.
I gave you another chance.
Hey, is that, oh, I see.
I think I hear a sweet summer,
sweet summer in the background.
Is this summer?
Summer?
Thank you, I no longer.
Okay.
Well, he's literally a retarded.
He's literally a retarded person.
Like, I mean, I gave him,
how many chances did I give him just then?
How many?
Till like relieve himself. I wanted the sweepy voice. No, I wanted a
New character summer. No
Okay, if I don't hear Christine. Oh, it's Christine. Is this Christine? Hold on
I think I hear Christine coming if I don't hear Christine. I
Swear to fucking God Arthur. You're never coming back again. Okay. I don't hear a Christine right now
Okay, I'm banning you from the chat, you're banned.
Never come back again.
Never, ever, ever come back again.
Felipe, thank you.
You are a stud.
Because he wasn't playing, okay, here's the thing.
It's called improvisation.
It's like you play along with the bit if you don't then the bit is ruined and I look stupid and shit like that
And I gave him like how many chances to just give him
I'm banning him from your stream artist. Hey, you figure it out. I'm Arthur you figure it out
You have to figure out your band from streamer now, too. That's what you get
He called improv. Here's the improv. It's not very complicated. It's acting. It's like
I say something and you just agree with what I say
and then you take it a step further.
It's like, it's such an easy thing to do.
And he knows how to do these voices.
And he's refusing to when I like specifically I'm like,
I'm like basically walking him through it and stuff, right?
I'm basically to say, just do this voice.
Why isn't he allowed to impersonation? No, he is but he wasn't gonna do them. He was just doing Arthur. I don't like Arthur
I want to hear
sweep in summer
And so I don't want to hear stupid Arthur. Hello
Like I tried to send you a picture, but it won't allow me on discord because we're not friends on it
Okay, why send me a friend request thing. I did. Well, let me look at it. I don't see a friend request. It's not there
Hold on you're just a psyche awaken or cult of psyche or psyche. I think it's cult of psyche now
It's it's pending. Yeah, it's pending. No, no send a cult of psyche not psyche awakens a psyche awakens
It's that's called of sight what you would a AI image of you with long brown hair
Yeah, I'm Jesus. I'm literally Jesus, but I don't see infirmary quest. Okay, let me check. Do you have a heart is the heart?
Do you have a heart before your name?
Yeah
Yeah, I said, I said a pendant, but I think it's a lot of I got it. I got it. Okay. I accepted it
Okay, send me the picture is it of Arthur in his speedo? Oh
My god
Yeah, and it's crazy because she deleted it right she because she was going to
Kate the turtle and she had deleted it before anybody can see and she posted a
picture of herself which is AI it's a AI image it's a AI image and she's saying
that it's not an AI image the woman on the right is like like a supermodel
right and that she said that was her a few months ago when she was at the beach
I promise like she said that's her yeah hold on let me I don't believe it I
don't believe it this is impossible this is fucking impossible hey Alex this is
what Christine says is her you listen this is a Christine's image are you
ready for this I don't think you're ready we know what she looks like no you
don't until you see this all right go ahead go ahead
So on the left is a real Christine and on the right is her AI generated image. Okay. I think it went through
And this is what she looks like, okay, are you ready to see I'm ready. I don't think you're ready for this
Do I have to buckle up? Is it that bad? Yes. Look
She says look
Yeah, that is her actually that's her when she was younger
Yeah, that's her like 20 years ago. She shows those pictures all the time that is her
But she's saying she's saying that this she's saying that it's recent the one
The one on the left is reason what that one on the right
I know I know the one on the right not the recent one. I know
If that was the reason my man, I would have been all over that
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah, that's not an old heck. Hey, I'm sorry. Okay, kid. I'm sorry
Yo, brother, I'm gonna I'm gonna take care of the cat food and the flea collars
But it's not gonna be from your Amazon list and I'm just gonna work with that shit now. All right, but that means
I can't do that is Christine on the right. That's her. That's her. That's her
Can we talk on discord privately? Okay? I want to talk to you about some things. Is there some things?
I'm telling you. She's a little hearty back in the day
She show shit of her in bikinis and shit
That is like
Christine Chirlington or something I have cat food, but I have a cat food on the wishlist in case people are saying
Oh, I'm gonna spit on drugs and stuff. You have white food for the little little fur balls. Oh, she claimed it was two months ago
What?
Two months ago. How no?
No, no, she claims brother the picture on the left that she came up that's her came up about three months ago
The shit on the left
Like look at the neck look at her neck with the and look at the neck on the beach photo
All right, so she comes up all the time with us all the time in her kitchen
Another panel and that's her
The woman on the right is not a nine a grandmother with nine children
They're getting grandchildren in any universe. I've ever heard of
I'm wrong. What's wrong? What am I wrong about?
Are you okay? Are you gonna be in a good state of mind to get the uber fucking you the cat bullshit when I send it?
All right, but I can't do the McDonald and the catch it the catch it's a fifty dollar hit
That's the nice McDonald's. I'm good. I have the burger still and I have all right food
So I'm gonna send you all just the flea collars in the food
So it's okay. I can make I'm gonna say make make the woman on the left picture
I can say make her beautiful. I can do that. I can do that right now. I'll do it right now
I'll prove to you guys. I know how to do this shit guys
I'll, I'll do the AI of the image on the left. Hold on. I'll just say like, basically 30 seconds. I'm so fucking good at this. I swear to God. Guys, if you don't like know that I'm like fucking good, you have, where have you been? Okay, hold on.
I got it.
Okay, I'll just take a minute.
It said no response. Well, I didn't put it. Oh my god. It says no response. Well, I had me put through a different program
Again, but I can literally do it. Hold on. I
Need to do it through a different program. I think it was like the TOS that's too impossible or the I don't know
Let me see. I had media and put the make the woman on the left
I'm going to say 50 years younger or 50 years younger.
Let me see what it comes up with.
I can't believe, I can't believe what I'm seeing.
I am in fucking shock.
I can't make that edit to the photo.
The image is locked by age change.
If you want I came okay, okay. I'll say it's gonna get a porter make a painted portrait, huh? I
Guess they get too many catfish people and stuff so they can't do that legally so it's gonna make it
It's gonna make it into a portrait a painted portrait
Even even like she's breaking the AI when I try to do this
I can't even like make her younger with the AI. It's like saying. Oh, that's against some kind of law
This is shocking. I am absolutely in fucking shock
Well, it's crazy man. I can't believe that she would lie to everybody on salmon and saying that the picture was from March of
This year, you know, yeah, it appeared for a second and then it stopped and it's like I seriously broken the AI
I'm gonna try more time. Do you think it's because oh, okay never mind
I was gonna say you you only got one picture right the older picture
No, I guess I have to open it and I'm gonna just put that
I'm gonna make a single picture out of the old picture.
Hold on one second, I have to crop it, one second.
I have to crop it, and I'm gonna make it
into like a portrait, okay?
I'm gonna make it into like a,
I'm gonna crop the other woman out of it.
I'm just gonna say, paint a picture
of this woman for 50 years younger.
Okay, I'm gonna save it, okay, save as.
Say that okay. I got I got I got I got I got a cropped. Okay one second. I'm gonna say do a oil painting of
this woman
50 years ago, okay
That's what I'm gonna say. Okay
That's all I'm gonna say. Yeah, I'm telling you exactly. I'm gonna say it's not saying it says it's like illegals
Like what I did so far. Okay, okay?
Make okay, I have to say she's over it. She's it if you want to Kate if you want to just come up and talk to psych
I'll just leave you know I'm saying I just boy. I'll take it. You know, I mean, I'll take a breather
Okay, I got you I
Got it. Okay, so I think I was thinking like maybe she's like
50 and so maybe I said 40 years younger that would make it to you
So I think it's like so okay, so I think it's gonna I was but I think I thought she looked 80 years old in this picture
This is what she looks like now.
Oh my God, it looks like Swee- Sweepee.
Is this, she's Sweepee, you guys.
Guys, she's Sweepee.
Look at this.
This is the oil painting, 50 years younger, okay?
I hope the police aren't coming to my house
because I said, I mean, I thought she looked,
oh my God, look at this, guys.
Look what she turned into Sweepee.
Look at this.
This is Christine, a young Christine.
Oh my God.
What in the fuck?
It's sweep, it's literally sweepiest picture.
What in the fuck is going on?
I am so confused.
That's Christine
You can't do that she's a kid's busy right now L dose. You can come back. I mean, it's like I'm I can't I'm literally speechless
It turned into the sweet peas pictures. It does look like sweet peas. It doesn't look like sweet peas photos
That is shocking isn't that exact I'm sorry low key. I'm sorry low key. I'm not trying to be mean
I'm not, no, you're not even allowed to use the age filters.
She would be literally a sperm and an egg.
If she like said, I don't know, I don't know.
I can't go back any further than this.
That's Christine, good fucking God.
She's hot.
What happened Christine Christine? This is what the Sun does to you. Why were you why what why all the tanning and stuff?
You turned into
this lady on the left
But the way you turned into
Okay, I got a firm request. Okay. I got you. I got you. Okay. Let me let me out. I'm gonna check my discord
I mean, Jesus, I'm sorry guys, I don't mean to be like blasphemous or anything.
I got you, I got you.
Thank you.
Wow.
There's another one, I have another one guys.
I've actually more, these are other variations of it.
Look at how hot Christine was.
I mean, guys, look at this.
She could have been on a soap ball.
What happened, Christine?
You left yourself too long out in the sun.
Thank you, Alex.
Hey, Alex, me and the kiddies thank you
for the bottom of our hearts.
You are an awesome guy.
Thank you so much.
Look at this, guys.
I have more variations.
Look at this one.
Look.
Look at that.
Look how beautiful. Who is this woman? She's I think she's sweepy. Yes. It is Christine. These are
She's Chris. It looks just like sweepy
That's Christine guys look at this one
That's her
She's Taylor's she's Taylor Swift. She's literally Taylor Swift
What in the frickin frackety frick
I'm sure I'm gonna turn straight for Christine Christine
What happened?
What in the fuck happened?
Sydney Sweeney was general hospital or something young in the restless or something what the hell happened Christine?
What I
No, I did I did I did I did I
Have one more I have one more
Look at this. Look at this beauty right here
Guys, you're gonna be shocked. This is her look at this one. I
Turned straight I turn I accepted the very best
Wow
What in the fuck oh, hello, hi, how are you is it it's paper, right?
Is it paid for
It's not no, I didn't order that I'm sorry sir
My name is not Ronald McDonald no
No, no, my name is not McDonald's I swear
I didn't order it. It sounds like a prank, maybe?
I know, I think, but that's why it's a prank, because I didn't order it.
My name is not Mr. McDonald, I swear.
I did not, sir. I would pay for the pizza ahead of time.
Can you please block my address on the deliver list? Are you Domino's? Who's Pizza Police are you?
It's paid for?
Yeah.
Awesome.
But you're not going down the slide.
Hold on.
I think it's not wrong.
We're going down the slide.
It's paid for?
Yeah.
I'm just going to add you.
So you just said it's nothing to do with it.
I get pranked.
I can show you where I get pranked.
I'm not McDonald's, but it is delivered to the address.
So why are you sharing your information?
Well, I don't know how to make money.
Well, you're trying to fool me.
You're playing with me.
I am.
Are you?
Why would you?
Because you said it's not paid for.
And I said my name is not McDonald's.
It's not McDonald's.
If it's paid for, I'll accept it.
Your ID is McDonald's?
No, it's these.
Give you a picture of it, and you can-
No, no, it's not McDonald's.
Okay, it's not it's not you're not McDonald's, okay, but it's not well besides maybe I've made all living here
But they mess remember me saying if I were made as long as I live with them. I see them wrong McDonald's wait for
Okay, are you being home?
Can I have that word?
No, he's asleep right now.
He has a very busy day.
He's promoting Ronald McDonald.
You said he's asleep?
No, I said he's here.
He's asleep.
He told me not to wake him up.
I'm going to call in the support.
Okay.
I'll say it's okay if it's the right address and it's paid for.
Call support.
If it's not, then...
I said my name's not Ronald McDonald.
Right, so you know me, so I can't tell you.
No, but my boyfriend Ronald is asleep in the bed, and you might have had a gift delivered.
Now he'll be very disappointed if you don't drop it off.
He's asleep, he's passed out on pills.
Okay, you're just fucking with me then.
Oh my god.
Guys, I got a pizza from Jordash to Ronald McDonald.
Okay guys, listen to this.
I said, my name's Dodd-Romain Donalds.
And I said, is it paid for?
And he's like, no.
And so I said, OK, it's a prank then.
And then he said, oh, it is paid for.
And I went down there and I said, well, my boyfriend
Ronald is asleep.
You heard it all?
And he's not trying to give you the pizza.
That's crazy.
It's paid for.
Who are you going to give it to?
He's lying.
He's just a liar.
The pizza got away.
They should have used my real name. They should have used my real name
Right
I'm not married to him yet. Okay. I'm not married. We're engaged
And he's asleep right asleep. I
Told them he's asleep passed out on pills you heard
Yeah, that's me exactly trippin sip exactly
Right
Ronald is not gonna get his pizza tonight. Okay
This is the worst day of my life.
I am starving to death.
Now my boyfriend is gonna, Ronald will,
Ronald beats me, Ronald beats me.
Ronald's gonna be so mad when he wakes up.
He's gonna wake up probably tomorrow.
He's gonna be so mad.
Ronald's gonna use his refund.
Okay.
Guys, this is the worst day of my life.
Ronald, he will be.
Joe, Redez, I have a temper.
Do you ever know that?
You know that they have the worst temper
Ronald's gonna beat this shit out of me I
Do not have a burger. I have a whole burger in the fridge and I have half my fries. What's it Ronald beats me? Oh
It's not paid for oh, yeah, it is come on down
So you're messing with me
And I said, are you homophobic?
And he said, no.
I'm literally starving to death.
I mean, guys, look at me, look at me, hold on.
I'll take Christina off the screen for a minute.
I'm sorry, Christina docks you.
I mean, I didn't mean to share your modeling photos.
Eldo, literally look at me.
Eldo, look.
Wow, man, come on, man.
Wow, man, you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Can you order me a pizza, please?
What you mean? I thought the cash out here. What happened? Come on, man
Cash out those three dollars because they like my tats you it wasn't a bike
Somebody donated right somebody somebody
They said it in the chat
You also have a clap token and I'll make your video too if you want me to Ronald McDonald beats me guys. He beats me
I'm sorry Ronald. Oh my god, he's getting up guys. I think he's waking up. He's like where's my pizza? I
Am in trouble
It's okay
He has a big life insurance policy on his head. I'm gonna choke that
Yeah, no the cat stuff. I'm sure it's in the right name. It might be at the wrong address
I might have to run down the street and stuff. I'm shutting up. Okay. I'm shutting up. Okay guys. I was just joke
It's just joke
It was a joke. I could take a dick you guys can take a joke. Okay
Thank you Donator you now have a free clap token to use on whoever you want
And I'll make a video with you if you want to.
Okay, I'm gonna shut it down, I'm gonna shut it down.
I know it's fake.
The guy was like, had a fake, he had like a,
his eyes was like, well, you said your name wasn't McDonald's.
And I said, well, my boyfriend Ronald's upstairs,
you heard it all, okay.
Guys, Trippin' Sip or Tripp Kick, this better be clipped.
Cause I think, oh my God, oh, he's here.
Oh no.
You woke him up guys guys you woke him up. I need to put the banner up. I think he's calling from the other room
He's mad. He looks mad. He looks mad. You know, he's like he's a very terrible temper
Like I said redheads don't mess with the redhead. Okay. They're just
Irritable where's my banner? Okay, hold on one second. I have a banner to put up real quick or a
Media, hold on. Let me put up a thing. Oh
Is that it? No, hold on one second
You're gonna be an overlay here. Okay. Got it got it got it
Ronald's
Hey, yo, it's a pizza ready is the
Why were you why did you come out? Oh, he was
Where's the pizza? Where's the pizza?
He asked you didn't come out and hungry
Ronald, it's okay. I'm sorry Ronald. Don't don't you get out on me, please. Yeah, you call my name
I'm fucked up on Xanax. How the fuck am I supposed to hear you?
Ronald, I'm so sorry Ronald. It wasn't my fault. He said he couldn't deliver without your ID
What the fuck when the when the fuck do a pizza guy need a fucking ID?
I'm so sorry
I'm in the fucking room right now. I'm gonna fucking teach you a lesson
Take me up to the garage you getting locked me in there, please don't better go get me a fucking pizza then
I will guys. Can you please donate for a pizza? I gotta get wrong one right now
Or is it like he's gonna beat me to death almost I think I?
Paid for a fucking pizza now. Where is it?
He left he left. He said he was calling the police or door to go get him
Go get him unless you want another black guy
I think he left Ronald I'm so sorry wrong I think he left
Hey, we have a guest guest in the chat. Let's welcome. All right. Well fuck it
I'm a fucking take more Xanax than there better be a pizza here in two hours or you're gonna get beat
Okay, wrong. I run. I love you and I love your big your big up. Okay. Hello. No, we're tripping said
Huh what what who I'm eating food you are you eating food?
Yeah, I'm an apple pie right here. No eat it eat apple pie nigga
Yeah
Bum ass nigga, look at this nigga, he's in there.
Yo, yo, so I got a question though.
So, so you telling me that somebody clabbing with cash
and you didn't respect Amber's token?
I thought the token come first.
Tell me who clabbed him just now.
Okay, Amber.
Damn it.
He's playing me high as five, so he just used one.
He's playing me high as five.
Oh my.
He's playing me high as five, so he just used one.
It was a real woman doll.
Hey guys, do you believe in magic?
You're banned for 24 hours a man. Come back later. Nuka. Oh, somebody clapped them
Who I'm tokens play paper silo really cool guy. Oh, yeah
This isn't that funny, of course, it wasn't trippin stuff salmon, please
No one believes you
We all know was the real
Rob McDonald's
Yeah, he's banned 24 hours
Felipe W
Thank you for using your clap token. You're now poor clap tokens left. You have six months to use them
Plus, I'm gonna give you a video if you want to contact me
Yep. Hey, here's it. I like this comment right here
Do one of the definition of no life is doing a nine hour live and then immediately hopping on IG and discord chas
Wait, did he come on psyche's panel Sam and you to grow up man
Oopy oopy
Oopy oopy oopy
Sam and you've been you've been same and you just have punked
You heard Sammy he used your own your own clapping system to get you back
And he making money off of it. That's hilarious
That's how you do it site. That's how you do it
That's hilarious
All of my new pizza, just wait.
Absolutely. Oh, he said ten dollars. I'll do I'll do eight dollars. Are you going cheaper? That's not bad
That's a discount. Anyone want to do eight dollar clap token or if anyone has
It's free for Alex. It's free for
for
Two days also to give them to Felipe
Oh, I'm just getting a message right now for a moment.
Oh, I got a serious question too, Sykes.
Since you and Kate are in a verge of making up,
you're going to remodder up, you know?
What do you think?
I would do that.
I would do that for sure.
You would do that for Kate?
OK, I'll do that.
I would do that for Kate because, you know what, Kate?
I like Kate.
And I think Kate never did mean wrong.
And I probably, like, maybe offended her and stuff
like that, but I certainly do that for Kate.
So if Kate wants to comment and chat I will remodel her up right now if she wants to
Okay, hey, say man, I mean I'm gonna join you. Hey, say man. Do you believe in magic?
Only Ronald can do
And Ronald is great in bed. I love like grabbing his wig
Oh my gosh, my gosh
Sorry guys, my phone is going crazy
Wow
Okay, somebody else has the
Now the the tokens at the prices raised is $50 now because all the tokens have been bought for $10
You're right, I know you were mad at me the mod but Kate I'll talk to you about it
Because there is more stuff going on in the chat and stuff than was apparent and stuff and on that life
But we can talk about it privately. I'd like to talk about privately because there's other stuff going on
Okay, no, it's you know
Here's what I always said we can chat later. No, I always said I'm not
SUEWERCADAL and if anything happens to me, it's because something happened like it was that that's why I said
Know
No
Yeah, what's that later? Oh
Sham sham a man shaman
your sham
She said she hates me you know what well, maybe she was mad at me for some reason
But maybe like you don't need to like get involved in it because I understand
There's misunderstandings, but you know what for sure I hate you say man
That's for you, Samman.
It's kind of moonwalking all over your ass.
Okay?
Sham wow.
Sham wow, Samman.
Chululu.
You bitch.
Samman's such a bitch.
Oh, I'm doing something.
Good!
Please stay away.
Go away.
I never wanted you here. Everyone hates you here. Go away. Okay. He's banned Kate. I can't
He's banned
All right, now he's done with psych right?
Yeah, now you know how it feels the band to get banned to get clapped for money
You do it the sites I get clapped as soon as he go up there
Now now now he does it to you
And you got a problem. He doesn't like it so much. Does he now? He don't like it
Crack it Edward I don't hear him call me a bitch in a crackhead anymore. I don't oh, no, I
Get a lot. How will I ever get over it? I
Only had him here because I think people like like him kind of like fighting with people, but I don't care about that
Out to the child, you know again Christine out here lying on her body her age. She lied about her age for a fact
I believe she said she was like 50 something she like 60 something
Yeah, that's what i'm saying. She said psych a lot of you not she said she was 52 or some shit like that
two-year-old unless they were like started having
Children at 12 years old and the children had children was what her is 50 years old
Right exactly and then to the photo at the beach. She said that was taken in
March
Can you run the chat for a little bit? I have to go for a second. Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah. All right
so
So, yeah, I thought he's gonna end alive
He found out that Christine has a crush on site
And she might have a crush on site. I mean as much as she talks about the guy, you know
She might she might
And I know that bitch clapped me earlier and sandman took cash over a fucking token
When he talks about the token is comes first
So wait to wait decide you can go ahead scam that that was a scam. That was a motherfucking scam
But it's alright at the end of the day
I can come over here and fuck with site if not site
I can fuck with beta if not beta. Hopefully one day K forgive me
She unbans me and I can go over there. If not
It's cool. You know, I mean, but fuck saying man
Fuck that Yu-Gi-Oh playing motherfucka
I got the wettest brain on the internet and i'm proud
Okay
Yeah, and sep you got to use a motherfucking ought to talk to me. I didn't miss here shit
slow
Retarded motherfucker
Received the cash app
But at the end of the day the tokens come before the motherfucking cash app and he took the fucking cash
Because he don't like a motherfucker, but if it was any other person that motherfucker would have said I gotta respect the token first
We got a respect the token first
Shululu token first
Token come first first token token first
Nigga scan me
Nigga scan me. I'm not letting it go
Thank thank God for Felipe for clapping them all fucking same man that made my day now
He know how I feel if he go to beat us if be to go live he gonna get clapped there, too
Nigga greedy man. All he care about is money. I should clap him, but I'ma keep my money
I'ma keep my money. He love getting that money
And they still get to play the content that he want to fucking play
But I remember when he first started this shit
He said anybody that clap me for a hundred they can pick the content and and they can run the show
Now it's fucking different. I can get clapped, but I get to still play my fucking big tea content
buddy
Somebody come up here, man.
Sight getting dicked in the butt by Ronald McDonald
and I'm here fucking entertaining y'all.
I'm not with all that, man.
He got two minutes.
Well, he walked away trip. Uh, you're trying to come up. Oh
He would you try to come up earlier trip and he didn't let you up
Cuz he ain't he ain't around so he wouldn't be able to let nobody up right now
But if you telling me he was up here, you was in the in the backstage earlier when he was talking damn
But right now he ain't around so he ain't he ain't let nobody up
Oh, you, I was just back gay, like, aw, shit.
Oh, I'ma say something to him when he come back.
I'ma ask him.
I'm sure he'll let you up, though.
He ain't got a problem with you.
Damn, I wish I would've known.
Shit, I would've said something to his ass.
Cause it is showing that somebody,
it's showing that somebody else backstage.
It's showing that somebody else is backstage.
It says two people.
Oh, it's Alex Sander.
Oh, okay, okay, yeah, yeah.
I can see that it's another person back there.
He need to give you a fucking stream yard.
What you call it?
Like he did that one girl.
Very good.
Oh, okay. I see what's going on that. I got you. I got you. I got you. That's what he went. Okay. Okay
All right. Well, what you get him a litter box talk to me. Oh
Okay, okay. Okay. Oh shit. Damn. All right shit. Oh
Shit, okay, I see why he keep you around
God, dang. That's why.
He getting the delivery, man.
He be back. He getting the delivery, man.
And that ain't the pizza.
Oh, damn.
He ain't getting no pizza.
Damn, how many boxes you ordered? Why are you taking so long?
Damn so you've been damn so you the one I've been feeding on fucking cats you come up here when you when he come back
Alex come up here when uh
When you come back man, I got questions for you, man
I question
That's why
just so you're not like doing it in any way.
Man, I ain't talking about shit in a turd, man.
But why is this man taking so long for cat food?
Alex, he coming back? Is you on the phone with him? Where he at, man? Damn.
So who's supposed to be danking Chad?
Nah, he uh, damn, oh hell nah, bruh
Like why I don't get it though why he can't wait for a doorknob like the pizza like when the pizza came I don't get it
Why he got a I don't get it. I don't get it
I don't get it man. Why he can't wait like the pizza like the door right there by the couch
I said, there ain't no songs, huh?
Yeah, like yeah, I can't do no one-man show, you know what I mean? Unfortunately, I
Ain't got no no no no control to play videos and nothing
Okay, so why why can't they deliver it straight to your door?
Like I'm confused man
Ah, man, I'm not good ain't not really going on right now. I'm not I'm no I'm not jerking off
What you need emergency
Oh, an emergency site.
We already was told what you're doing here, Derek.
Alex already said he's getting your cat food, man.
Ivana, come up here and sing real quick.
Ivana, come up here and sing, baby.
Come up here and sing to me.
Sing some karaoke with me.
I'll tell I'll tell psych to play a little beat for you
What you like singing in country a little bit R&B
Talk to me by now what you like to say
JB needs me right now
This thing amber sings too, I know embers thing
Damn, bro, come on, man.
Damn, y'all talking in cold?
Come on, man, what's going on, man?
Faking Alex talking in cold right now.
Damn man
I'm kind of sorry they clap saying man because he got caught man. He thought he fucked up man
He didn't follow a system with the clap shit
He was supposed to respect the token before the before cash
He says that shit with a passion every fucking lie
He always says he respect token before cash and then they could play the shit out of me, bro
Play this shit out of me Sam and if you watching you didn't be dirty
You know you did me dirty nigga cuz you respected cash before a token that shit crazy man
Because if it was the other way around nigga, you would have respected every time I got clapped you would have respected the cash
Before that token that somebody used
Shit crazy, man. Fuck that nigga man. Now y'all stuck with him all night
Hopefully hopefully be to go live and take all his viewers like last time
Fucking faggot
Sike, where the fuck you at? Damn, maybe like
You could have just waited for the month, but like you ain't got a tracking
Motherfucking change my picture
Então, bá maçã, vá, eu dou foto, ó, hein?
Oi, Lu! Oi, mo...
I'm a big clip and I like to fucking do big T's dirty words.
I cried because my mama didn't say happy birthday to me.
And I had to cry to somebody, but actually she was my best friend.
And now we're not cool.
But yeah, I like to cry because mama forgot to say happy birthday.
And I asked for money and she didn't give me money for my cable bill.
Yeah, fake lips
Hello, my name is Chris Tate, and I say I'm 32, but I'm really 72.
And I smoke fucking Marlboro 100s about a quart in a day.
I pretend to hate psych because Vita don't like psych
and I want to fit in with everybody at 72 years old.
I got fake boobs, I have no husband,
I lie and say I have a husband
because I don't want people to think
I'm a lonely old hag, Christine.
Hey, y'all, I'm KK and I only stowed from Walmart because I had to feed my child and I needed to I
Was on my period I needed tampons and it was July 4. So I had to steal a couple fireworks
Yes, I have no lips
Juice did pay for my lips, but it didn't work
It only lasted a couple days and my neck. I know I have none KK
Yes, bitch Empress Janet here never was a hoe always rich bitch status. I do not live in Section 8. I
Used to do I used to date a jailbird, but that was the old me now
I'm the new me my teeth are fucked up my lips are big, but I'm still a bad bitch bad bitch status Empress
Hey guys chicken snakes here. I sleep on the floor. I know by the litter box by the way
Yes, I got Janie written by side my tits. I'm just a groupie always will be a groupie my meds
Colana pen
Xanax I
Love it. I drink here and there and
I love YouTube's
chicken snakes
Yo, yo, yo, this is Julio saying me as brother.
I do look like a smurf, but I don't care.
I'm that man.
I used to be with War Dog,
and I'm scared to go on pain on there
because I got a soft tone voice.
I talk like a bitch.
J Bro.
Hey, bitch, I am the queen of doxin. I love to dox my ex friends
I love to dox my enemies. I dox dox dox
I sniffle a lot because I'm a cokehead and I do a lot of coke
So when you see me on ETC zebs, please say hi to me if I sniffle just know I
Do a lot of cocaine
peps
Oh my god, it's too big
Hey guys AI Christine here, I'm a bad bitch. You see I really don't look like this
But with a little AI touch up. I'm a bad bitch. You hear me a bad bitch
But this is what I really look like.
A ugly has been fake nurse.
Okay, this is me.
Like it or hate it?
Yes, my neck look like it's fucking melting.
What's the problem?
My cheeks look fucking blushy.
I look like a old wrinkly hag.
Love me or hate me.
This is me.
Yeah, yeah, it's Tommy James my neck off. This is me man. Hi as a kite as always
Only did a couple fucking pills smoked a little with a weed, but this is me see J
Tommy James man. Hi as a kite always on forever to the day I die
I'll be doing IRL later. Catch me then later
I'm back, baby. It's J bro who aka Julio aka broom gang. Is this my little twin or not? Let me know chat
What is this a smurf?
Is this my twin? Let me know chat J bro out
Monies
What's up, dude? You hear me the guys like almost there. I'm gonna drop. He's
That's up. Yeah
No, I'm here, I think I Alex said he was leaving
I'm done. I'm done, man. I'm tired, man. I'm done.
I'm done.
I'm here, though.
Okay, y'all gotta send me y'all gotta hit me up on discord cuz I don't die if I had think that is trust me
I would have I would have definitely done thing that is I don't have him
He would have been a good one
I was ready to do beta I ain't gonna lie to you I was holding off I was holding off on beta
It wasn't gonna be nothing crazy though, you know, just gonna act like beta. That's it. I was about to do beta though. Oh
Yeah, I still I do got juice the whole she was here. Oh my god. Why didn't I do juice the whole hold on man?
I think I still got him. That's it old
Before psyche get back I
Still got juice the whole I'm not doing the brother though. I
Do juice I'm not doing this brother
I guess I didn't go down for or I got a couple people I
Got sweet ass fucking look at this one sweet. I said man
Cupcake ass nigga saying man
Fruit loop ass nigga saying man teddy bear loving ass nigga saying man crown wearing ass nigga saying man I
Brows on fleek cuz he just got a dumb ass saying man
Never will look like this in his motherfucking life ass saying man
I forgot I had this shit.
Hell though. Oh my god. Yes, sir. What's going on, man? I had my last one. I could find just the whole book
Special delivery
That's much to everybody
Alice's man of his word
Wow, that's what's up. What kind of food will we got to figure it out because it gotta be that expensive brand
Oh, he got it friskies. He really got the friskies
That'll last about a good week cuz you've got like four cats, you know what I mean?
Oh, yeah, something
I got flea collars, too.
I see some flea collars, I think.
I was doing a little acting, man.
I got this last one, then I'll be done.
You know what I'm saying?
If you are, you know what I'm saying?
Oh, this is an acting.
I have another picture of Christine, too.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely.
This is a new one.
This is from Idol Up They Want Me To.
To give the name out and stuff, but let me see. I need to just go back. Let me see. Oh, yeah
Hey, it's thing Canadian brother thing that is yeah, it's me man
I'm I look constipated in this picture, but trust me. I'm not I just sit on my tea all day
I sit well I sit on my tea and I and I bother beta harass beta and think that I own beta
But I I really don't I I'm alone
I got a record, a criminal record that I do not want Eldo to find, Psyche.
Because if he finds it, then you will disown me and Bita will disown me.
I have tricks that are okay. I'm going to get these on the cats right now.
Psyche, won't you be my lover?
Sure, Eldo.
No, no, no, no. Dang.
Oh, it's medicine. It's medicine. So I'm going to give them a little on their neck.
Give them another neck and stuff.
Let me get on the door right now.
No, there you go psyche rub my ball head psyche rub my ball
Like the fucking the Buddha you rub your belly. It's I rub your bald head. Yes, but I sip on my tea
Nice game beaty-bop a little I'm gonna get my scissor
Okay, got it. Okay, Lola got it. Okay, now Rudy's going to have one for Rudy.
They're not freak. They're not flea collars. They're just they're they're they're plea medicine.
And so I'm going to put them on like cats neck. Okay, got Lola.
Hi, baby
Did you read did you read the instruction psych or you already used that before you just drop it in their neck
You just put it behind there behind their neck where they can't lick it off
Okay, now is it is this a banable offense? They said are you gonna put it on yourself? Is that a banable offense?
You can time them out for 10 minutes
Alex
Yeah
Okay, got a little okay. I got Rudy
I got Lola and Lenore.
I got you next, but once you're sleeping,
I'm gonna get you.
Don't get in my skin.
I didn't.
Good stuff, Alex.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Alex.
How's it going?
You're awesome.
Gonna maybe get a coffee soon, another couple drinks,
and go ban my, I'm gonna ban them.
I just said time and mouth.
I don't, there's no time out, sorry now.
He said time I'm out. Yeah
No, I can't
Yeah, we would guess welcome my special guest all the way from New York is a king of cocaine. He's the most famous shoe designer you've ever met
Yeah, yeah, no, no
No, hold on no flea colors because I ordered a
It's like a liquid medicine and I just you just put it on the cats next and then it lasts for like a few months
It's like a medical collar because I'm about to order collars. I want to see collars around their little neck
It's like medicine the medicine last a long time. I'll tell you what it's like our
Pet armor plus and then see this is like little like has a little three. It's a
That's for three months three months. Please. It's for please
so it's like an invisible flea collar yeah yeah yo hold up where lady b because lady b always
want to talk this smack on site that he don't take care of his cats where you at the medicine is
better than flea collars flea collars are kind of like just like a like almost like a decoration
kind of oh it is all right i was losing my mind i was about to call the gang go crazy like bro you
got the wrong shit
But it was a nice thing, all right, cool.
Rudy has it on, Lola has it on.
Lenora's too wise to it, and so she,
and then I like squirted like three-quarters of each one.
He's on.
And so I can put the rest on tricks when he gets back,
and this will be back.
Yeah, Alex, calm and collected now, you'll be chillin'.
Katrina, also I know like, I know you were like,
you were kind of defending me and Christine's.
I listened to the transcript and stuff,
and Katrina was cool.
And so, yeah, we're all good.
I just hope you forgive me, because you're like,
I know you're kind of like a troll and stuff,
like, but you admit it, that's the whole thing.
She defended you?
She defended me a little bit, you know?
It's like, she was kind of like,
kind of listening to them and letting them,
yeah, but she was like, you know.
Yeah, he's an MVP for the flea medicine even worried about that well, okay
I do like I like I do have like a flea comb and I do comb them of it
But this is good. This is like even better
You know, it's like and I appreciate it. I know you're an asshole
Yeah, because you said that and I appreciate that because no one else with everyone else is like I'm so perfect
And I'm like, you know this great person and you're like hey, I like I'm an asshole
And I like I like to fuck around with assholes and all that guy's
Yeah, it is offensive and you got wet food too. I have wet food too. I mean I went to the store
I got this like this thing today, and I got them. Oh, you went to go buy it
No, no, no, no, no, I went earlier today, and I got like I got a bunch of cans
Got some party mix, and I got a big thing of you know, I think cats
I buy I buy cat food before I buy it for myself
But this is like yo, but it's like not like
Cap it's like it goes quick, you know, and so it's like it's just like really appreciated
that, you know, Alec, I mean, definitely you're going to be eating it very soon, you know?
You don't gotta worry about food now, you know, at least for the cats, right?
Yeah, no, but the cats are always fed. Is this a thing?
Regardless, right?
Why is cat food? Like, you know, it's like, the cats are always fed. Like, you never see the
cats, but I'm really worried about Tricks now because Tricks has not been here since yesterday,
and I call them and he usually comes running when I call and stuff.
And so, I'm kind of worried about Trix a little bit.
And Lola's acting like really like a little bit.
I think she's like kind of like a mom,
because she, well, she is Trix's mom,
but she's kind of like getting really like a little,
and she's a little bit worried
because he usually back faster than this.
But let's all say a prayer for Trix.
And I think he's fine.
I just like, you know, sometimes he's been like,
You know, he's getting a little old. He's like two years old and you know
So I worry about tricks. Hey, look at Lenore has a flower petal. You're playing with the yellow roses like there's
There's the flowers. There's just Lenore
Nor
Here we go. That's your oldest cat, right?
Tricks is tricks is your oldest, uh, kid
He's the youngest Lola's his mom and then I have um, you know an old man Rudy is the oldest
Oh, yeah
So, okay. Okay. I'll look this means take my boyfriend's here. I'm sorry. All right long hold
Hey, yo Alex. I appreciate you getting the kitty shit. I appreciate it
Okay, I know they came from I know they look on the kitty shit Alex, but yes, but real shit though
Where the fuck my pizza?
Ronald the guy left he said it wasn't paid for then he said it was but he wouldn't give it cuz you were there my pizza
I don't want to hear it. I know I'm so sorry Ronald Ronald. Don't hit me
Hello
Where's where is the pizza? I I'm gonna I can make you a pizza
I have some English muffins and some cheese and a can of like, um
What the fuck I've catch up. I paid $30 for a pizza an hour ago
Can you call? Can you can you call because they didn't need to see your ID and I say I had all your magic
I want me to fucking call
Yeah, can you call please?
What are you good for?
What are you good at my whole butthole, okay? You can do it. Oh, no, no
Every have been requesting that you said you said yeah, you said I you said you wanted I want pizza not butthole
I'll put the pizza on my butthole
No
No, you're so hard to please you're worse than the hamburger
At least he's like, you know, he's versatile
It's just gonna get the fucking brass knuckles out and beat the shit out of you if you don't get me that
Like how we do it in the Bronx
Ronald stop it
Stop it, you know Ronald's actually just bronze bird and in white makeup in a white piece. You know that guys
Yo, it's me bronze bird. Oh shit. Yeah, now I've given away his identity
cracker
I'm a cracker mofo. Hey Lenore, do you want some of these treats here?
What up my niggas, it's me
Hey, the end of Ron told you not to call me the end word or my chat the end word. I got in trouble for that already. Stop it. Stop it, Ronald.
I know you're white as can be
but
You're also black
I'm black where it matters. Hey, yo
Yeah, oh my god, Ronald has the biggest cock. I've already man. I've ever been with it's big white
All right, enough of the gay shit. Where is my pizza dough?
Squeezing it makes a honking sound
Ronald drives the coolest car to you. It's little hold on the whole time. He said you laying in his bed naked
My pillow is covered in white and red makeup. He'd be trying to suck my dick. I'd be brushing it off
He's a real boyfriend, where's my piece? I want a piece of the pizza. He wants you to eat the cheese off his cock psych
I let him I let him call I let him call me and my his boyfriend so I have a place to stay but oh
My god, use these psych. I it's actually cute. It's just cute and it's cute
I'll make up this is not cute 45. Yeah, that's how we got up the streets
All right, enough of this fucking joking shit. Where the fuck is my pizza?
He was hanging his hands with an Indian guy, he based the guy, and he said, I can't live there anymore.
And so I said, I'm gonna beat the fuck out of you, you fucking cheater.
Chew, stop it. Get out of here. You're done.
What? Wait, that was Q?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
I saw you got him off the street.
I did not.
Yo, Q role playing.
He took over Arthur's job.
I know.
He took over Arthur.
Arthur stopped role playing.
I was like, Arthur.
Am I talking to Christine?
He's like, no, it's Arthur.
I was like, okay.
Then I said, I'm talking to Sweepe.
He's like, no, it's Arthur.
I said, I'm talking to Bita.
And there was Arthur every time.
He wouldn't even pretend anymore.
So Q, so Q, Q called me and he's like, I need a place to live.
Oh, that's not cute couples like they say
Kate Kate where were you last night when you're like that wasn't Amanda Erickson as the safe of March by the way
Q is calling me John and it ruining my bits
Kate you're after a bit. He kept ruining the bit
So that was my sweet revenge. Okay. It wasn't a guy that wasn't Q
That was the real Ronald McDonald
It was
No, it's the real the guys you believe magic that only Ronald can do
Who's trip? I don't know any trip. I just know trip kick and that's not oh, yeah, yeah tripping said that's tripping said
He told me he was coming up here
Guys I need to do a class on improv what you do is you just agree with me whatever I say. Oh
Okay, now, okay, I was tripping fuck
Let's do it again. Let's do it again. Let's do it again. Okay. Okay. Never never mind. It wasn't he said it wasn't him guys
It's called improv. Here's what improv here. It's really easy. There's like three rules to it or two rules
I have to do is you agree you take it a step further and then you keep agreeing
There's just three rules to it. You don't say oh, you're really
Me say my real name is me say my real oh you're John. Oh, it's chip and sip
Guys, yes, but we're playing improv. It's okay. Yeah, it was okay. We'll next time. We'll get it
Yeah, we'll get it next time. Oh
Can I can I suck on your elbow?
No, no, but but I think Arthur would let you do that Arthur said no
He said I could only like come in his clown shoe
Ronald
He said I can watch his wrestling video if I can find it and jerk off to it, but I can't find it. Can you give me?
Arthur's wrestling video, please
Yeah, yeah, I'll find it. Yeah, I'll find it. I'm gonna find his wrestling video
Okay, you just earn another you just earn another clap token. Okay. Thank you. Thank you
Welcome. But you have to like
give me the video actually.
Okay. Once you get the video,
you'll get another clap token.
So, you'll get, you'll have
three. Got you. Got you.
You said you had one more image of Christine right site remember you said the hold off on it
Yeah, I think I saw it on I think I saw something on discord. Let me just check once again
I think I got a message on this work Rob. Why are you making that face of me?
Okay, that disappointed devil face of me. I hate that's my least favorite base cuz it's like
It's like it's like oh what the fuck it's kind of like that face. I don't like that
I like them. I like the laughing till I cry face. I like
Okay, I found that I found I found it guys. Do you see I guys you want to know I found Christine's actual photo? I
Have my god, cool photo. Okay guys get ready
This is not AI. This is her
Okay, the younger and and then today
You thought my girl picture was bad after a year. Look at Christine. Oh my god. I'm gonna show you guys
You'll be shocked. It'll be a shock
And this is not a joke guys, this is real.
Oh my God, you do go, oh my God.
Look at it, look at it, just look at it.
She's trying to say, bro, this is what I'm saying.
She going at Kate.
She picked the picture that where Kate was fucking crying.
She's not even crying and she looks way worse than Kate,
bro.
She's trying to look good. I think I think Christina sweepy on a voice changer and she's been trolling me this
I mean, I'm sure now because that's sweetest photo. This is a picture sweepy was sending me. That's crazy
I know I talked about you. She talks about your nails. She talks about your beard
Everything she talks about. Oh, he's not a trust buddy. It's paid on Friday. He's the last four. I know it's she's like
She doesn't know anything about anything, but she talks all this shit.
Christine, you want to play with the big boys now?
Welcome to the panel verse, okay, bitch?
Okay, now you're in.
Okay, I know, Ivana, is that shocking?
For my thing everybody know what I do it is cool
But the thing is the fact that I see that she said here lying
You're not gonna come to a community and think we just fucking idiots
I don't know if that's what she do over there in her community
But she can't come over here and line us talk about this was a last month in March when I was at the beach
You know I'm saying like are you are we just supposed to play dumb?
She has nine grandkids and she looks like this
Crazy. Yeah, this that's Christine. It's like that's Christine. This is her. That's what she looked like right now
That's Christine right now. According to her
That's her and no I mean guys I wish I was kidding look at this look at her
It's like look at this. Look I would have sex with this woman. Oh my god. Oh my god
All you remember about day night is Elvis butthole, but I would have sex with this one
Your what the fuck that could come on. How you gonna go from Christine to my asshole when I saw you twerking
I can't I don't forget that. Why you keep talking about my ass man. It looks good
Even they're saying yesterday. They saw the thing that stood up and they're like, oh, well
You have a nice butt, but
Eldo has trip where you at trip trip. Where you at trip come on trip
You don't you playing me trick cuz you say he's gonna come up your trip. Where you at trip? Yeah
That's okay guys. This is Christine
Would have sex with this woman. I would I would lick her pussy out. I don't care how big it
I don't care if it's bigger than um, then six I would lick her pussy this woman right here
But then is it but then is it this woman right here? Oh, is it how is this the same woman? I don't understand
What's going on here is there something going on weird how is that woman this woman?
AI is fuck you. She has a husk. She admitted she said her clit is bigger than
then I'm sick dick and I do believe that but I
All I think about a husk I think about I
Open it up and there's like boiled corn inside so that to this. Oh
My god
You're gonna give me a warning so I come on you thought I thought it was Halloween for a second
think no we can't move on no no we're gonna be on yeah we're talking about
this topic because this is it and cool she's lying she's talking about sight
she's clapping site he's clap yeah Johnny my channel take it down and then
she's mad that maybe that's it maybe that's an AI age picture well I'm gonna
do another picture one second I'm gonna do her picture I'm gonna actually make
These chicken cakes 2.0 she sound does she sound like you know chicken cakes, right site?
Yeah, doesn't she sound like chicken cakes or voices shit
She might be I don't know if she's chicken kicks or not. I just don't know for sure
I'm telling you bro
I said that shit from the get-go trip that she sound just like chicken cakes and chicken cakes is already a non
People do not like chicken cake. So that from the job was all but I knew she was always off
Bro, like she's sitting here threatening this to strike people then we already that's a no-no
Then she's sending her line about her looks like like we supposed to be retarded.
We're not dumb like we see what you really think we got people like fucking tripping seven and other people in this community that they
Like come on, bro. We're not we're not stupid. Kate know how to investigate shit like that picture straight up 100%
Now chat she did say she removed somebody from that picture. So she's gonna use that as an excuse
There was somebody wearing that picture
Here's what what here do what happened if we were to make her 40 years old doing see this picture
Yeah, yeah, are you sure it might be shopping?
It might be a little bit too much for us to take right now. I don't know. This is her four years older
Are you sure you want to see it? Yeah, I'm ready for her. Oh
my god
That's more like it psychic
That's more like it this is it
think so I need this this is her yeah this is Christine look oh my god
Christine I'm sorry I didn't mean I didn't mean I said it as a beaker for it
because that other picture of you was AI too I know I'm an expert in
AI you think I'm just fell off the shirt I'm truck yesterday I know
She she's like a 90-year-old grandmother that was her 50-year-old photo then she shows us his 20-year-old photo
Look at look guys. Can you see the difference guys? Look at the difference. This is the number one. This is when she was
Yesterday oh my god
Kate Kate, I'm gonna send this to you in discord. Okay, Kate Kate do whatever you want to this picture. I don't care
Okay, this woman tortured me on her live. Okay, so Kate. I'm gonna send this to you right now
Because I love you Kate. I do love you Kate. I'm gonna send this picture to you Kate
I don't forget the my side, you know since you up here now
Okay, I'm gonna send you this picture and you know whatever you make her
Whatever character you want to make her I don't care anymore
Don't care. I'm sending it to you right now. I'm in mod you right now
There you go
Oh, okay shit, well she doesn't want to okay. She doesn't need to be okay. Well
Only if you if you ever do
Because you're a great mod, but but rather have as a mod as a friend and so
We'll talk. We'll talk privately. We'll talk. We'll talk later. Okay
Yeah, oh, I'm getting I'm getting a message. Oh, you know, and I had a respect for Kate
That's all you don't say cuz that you know, she had your back. That's all that's why I brought it up
Hey, you know me like I'm not even trying to be funny at this point, you know, I'm saying but I'm just like maybe
the way he talks about you honestly like
Anonymous an anonymous friend has sent me this picture. It's like I apparently YouTube flagged
An image is AI. I just want to show you this image I have right now.
Oh, wow.
It was flagged as AI.
Because it's AI, right?
That's crazy.
Let me see.
Made with AI, it says.
And she trying to sit here and fucking say it's not AI, bro.
Or she's trying to say that if it shows up as that, it's because she took her family relative off.
Like why are you
Grandchildren on the left. I was like, oh, there's her granddaughter. No, she said that was her
That's crazy
Picture 1984 how about like 19 like 38? I mean, I mean, oh my god
Nope, it looks official to me. Let me look at this closer
I'm gonna look at it closer on the look at her neck. Look at the difference in her neck her neck
That's a neck. I thought that was chicken skin. Oh my god. It does look like chicken skin
And I'm not gonna lie when she was younger. She she was. I see I'm not gonna
That was like that but we're not in the 18th century anymore. I'll go
I mean eventually people do get older and stuff and they start to sag a little bit, but yeah us
Yeah
What is going on? I don't I don't understand
This is her trying to attack Kate trying to like say oh look at me and then look at you
Have you ever seen Hocus Pocus when like they have a Sanderson sisters, right?
And they like old like recoded hags and then they all do like this period blood spell and they're beautiful again
That's what happens
Yeah, they either like they I think they like steal it like a like a you know woman or 20s period blood
And they rub it all over themselves, and then all of a sudden they're gorgeous again
Have you heard of that
No, I've seen the movie. I didn't know it's very a blood. Yeah. Yeah, it was period blood. It was period blood. I
Got I figured this all out because I dated a woman to a period blood in my spaghetti and all of a sudden a woman
Yeah, and in 2012 I dated a woman for three bus years of which oh my god. Yeah a real woman
Yeah, a real woman. I actually you've been in you've been in vagina. You're you've been in
I stuck it in and out and then I put my hand in there and
Like Niagara Falls, and then I had to throw in my couch. Oh my god
Because I would lay down on the couch streamers later and it would make a squishing sound because it was still wet inside of it
But it smelled a little bit like pee
My whole hand the whole hand went up there because she had like an elephant in yoga or the comma sutra
They say you have a you have a camel vagina a horse vagina or an elephant's vagina
She had the elephant vagina like it's in my whole hand in there. I got I wish I was kidding and it's embarrassing
But yeah
It wasn't the camel, but it was the elephant vagina she had.
I appreciate you representing the droop.
You know, I said, I see you got it on your screen.
You know what I mean?
You know, some people ban Drew from their channels, you know, like Gaia, he done it for a while
I think he stopped that because he's trying to fit back into the panel verse
But uh, perhaps I banned it. I think recently she said something about it. Yeah, I mean people would have been a droop
I don't understand. You know, I mean, it's like in in droop. We trust, you know
I'm gonna end this live and let me see who else is live because I'll send I'll send people over to their life
I don't want to be like struck for like harassment or like
As much he was live who's worthy of my
sending people
Okay, I would I'm gonna say and I know they're controversial
They're controversial. I like okay
I'm not gonna say who it is you can like go there and like leave or stay
But if you want to stay there say psyche set us and it's a rate
It's a friendly rate from psyche. Don't be rude over there. Okay. There's a link
Okay, man. I'll see you later, man. I'm a go-fi day. Okay, my bro, and I'll be back there. Okay. Okay. Thank you
I'm gonna delete this live and uh guys
You're all play a song on the way out. Hey guys. Thanks for my friends and stuff
Is that perfect? I'm not a perfect person I'm gonna play my new but this is the new psyche haters club song
Have a good day
Where the fake get loud when the views dry up
Gotta hate the one crook, he got a sermon half-baked
Say I'm praying for you while these screenshots get saved
Fake are concerned and their voice poison in the cup
Say I hate drama while they wind it up
Got pearls in a death grip, clutch, clutch, talk